Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think your love Can erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
Baby, I'm Father Scythe, the cat daddy
Scythe in the building, cars undead
Terror spread wild like a hacker on the net
Got linoa in the corner, claws out for lies
Tricks, plot and chaos with those cosmic eyes
Lola squeening on the chair, Rudy got flared
Mumbles in the mix, we don't play fair
Chat blowing out
Andromalleus, watchin' nightly
She a mystery queen DJ electric got the beat so clean
Beat her with the panther strength divine She teams chaos with the stare and the line
We don't do fake this tribe's too real We roast you kindly but the love's the deal
Got minds with swords keeping gates tight They swing truth like justice in the moon like
Gifted subs yeah the coke keeps growing Community wild but the energy's flowing
Welcome to Psycho 8
It's a family affair, it's dysfunction supreme
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Cards flip, candles drip, shadows in the mist
Trolls talk slick, but they cease to exist
We're half chaos, half or a cool flame
And every night's a ritual in Psyche's name
No scripts, no filters, no chillin' psych
We stream raw truth till the morning light
So grab your tea, grab your mic and vibe
We the strangest family
This ain't YouTube, this is an underworlds talk show, you are now initiated, father psyche is spoken, spoken.
This is Lilith Scorpiana and you're watching Psyche Awakens TV.
Psyche Awakens TV is a portal to the shadows of the soul where truth burns through illusion
and transformation demands courage.
Psyche rips open the veil of the soul, dragging you into the abyss where raw truth claws at
your core and transformation devours all fear.
It's a relentless plunge into that only the brave emerge reborn.
Enjoy!
What?
But...
Like Panera or I don't know. Yeah, sometimes the sometimes, you know
the computer takes liberties with the pronunciation
Hi guys, okay, what do I got? Oh
Hold on that better kind of
Oh, there we go. Perfect. Hi guys. I have a new song actually
But how many people are in here?
Let me see, hold on.
Eight people?
Can you guys like do me a favor and just like the stream?
Just like hit that like button and hit that,
like the positive like, not the like the one
with the thumbs down.
If you just, I mean, it's like,
because I get, I just don't get enough likes,
I don't think.
Or my eyeglasses a little bit crooked,
it's because I broke them.
But.
Still rock them kind of just like a little bit wonky eyed. Okay when I get to 15 people I will play the new video
It's a little surprise for somebody but that the person I don't think the person's ever been here you guys can probably guess
You've never been in the chat
But I still love them you guys
When somebody guesses all I'll play it, maybe
It's like a riddle, right
There we go
And no verse how about it's like it calls me like
CHK or something like checkie a week. I don't know. I
Just have to use this as a monocle now
This is how oh my gosh, why is it people leaving the Shannon here?
My gosh, someone was asking how to get the cure berry of his like, you know sex addiction
I was like just to find this woman named
Name cringe Osaurus and just go look at her. You want a one-up sex again?
Or I guess you Shannon would work too
Then I feel bad that I'm like so like mean, but they were like so mean to me, right? So
But I shouldn't, I should like, you know, kind of like,
I'm gonna break, because I am harsh sometimes.
Harsher than you would think.
But I'm a, I have like this like protect,
protective thing that doesn't let some people.
Oh, okay.
Well, let's just do, so, hold on.
Does Shannon know, if somebody has never been on the show
that I like, that they're kind of like a famous YouTuber
or a little bit, I would love her to come on the show,
I don't know what she ever was.
But she hasn't been on the show via video.
I'm a beast when I let loose, yeah.
I can be, but it's like, I don't,
but I like to be nice.
Even like when I like fight,
I feel bad sometimes after, you know?
Cause then I think,
what if I really hurt the feelings and stuff like that?
Cause you know,
some women are like really sensitive even,
and like some people that like dish it out,
like I'm like, beat is super sensitive, I guess, but.
I just don't know it's like she's like it's just like it's like different. She's like such a badass and then she's like
You know like a little crying
I know but this other person is kind of like that too like where it's like a little bit where it's like they are badass
But then you have like they're sensitive and like I've seen them cry over like you know people being mean and stuff like to them
So I don't know
Can you guys see that?
Anybody
Anybody anybody you're almost worse. I'm almost worse than you almost
Probably just as bad
Like my new this kind of a new logo. I think I like that one. I'm also on this website
Well, just for right next couple weeks. I have a trial on it, but it's you know, it's supposed to
Cook you up with it my advertisers. So on my community wall. There is like a really cool
media kit or whatever. Can anyone guess who it is? No one can guess yet?
I'll give you a hint.
But I don't want to give a hint because I know somebody will guess it. Oh my god, it's a really easy.
It's a woman that's very famous, but she's controversial.
She's never been on the show, but she's been on... I've been on her show.
She's very beautiful.
She sometimes is known as the queen of IRL or the captain, oh, not Christine. Nope. She's been on the show
This is somebody that's beautiful like really
I mean
Not not the Chris. I mean Christine is I'm sure you're a very nice nice woman
When she's not mad at me Christine when I was in be this chap be Christine was like fuck you
So in the chat she's like fuck you say get out of here like excuse me
Emma's been on the show and it was not only on the show, but she was also in the chat before
This person's never been in the chat that she's been on the show Alexander's been on the show
But you're almost you're getting like, you know, it's an E. J. Are her initials
Nobody knows
Okay, well 13 people so
Why gang is everyone talking about the Mexican gang that beat is that I just got a question like that
Okay, well the Mexican game that beat is in it's not really like a Mexican gang. I
Don't know what it were you hearing some of this. Where are you? Are you listening this beat on or something?
I don't know Erica. No her name is Elisa. Okay. Okay. I'll play the video home
Do you like it?
Do my best.
It was hard to edit, kind of,
but I did all the, I did all the, all these scenes,
like it makes, I had to cut a little bit out of it
because there was a little bit longer than I thought,
but I think it was pretty decent.
I think, did you get bored from the song?
I hope not.
At least.
I mean, maybe I'll change the song.
I'll play the other, I'll do the other version for you.
Let me see if I can find it.
Oh, yeah, I have it ready. I have it ready already.
I don't know if this is the same one. Hold on.
Makes like it's so better
The same one
Did you like the video?
I think I'm gonna put that one with the video.
The other song was a little bit longer.
Now, what do you have to criticize?
Probably bowling J-Doc.
Oh, what does that mean?
Going bowling with him?
And the ball's kind of dirty.
They give you the finger.
No, I gave it to Smash.
Smash up the finger.
Because he was, what did he say?
He said annoying stuff like, bo-bo-bullshit.
What does that mean?
Oh, hold on.
Oh, he's talking to Gotti maybe?
I don't know if you were talking to me.
I don't know.
I would just take this person.
Somebody docks me and send a pizza to me.
Well, you know, someone sent a pizza to Benny once.
Like the guy was named, he called himself Benny at first,
but then he changed his name to something else.
And then he, he sent Benny an actual pizza,
but he said like, he tried.
I think he, they've delivered the wrong kind.
They brought a barbecue chicken pizza,
but then he kind of liked it,
but it's like they don't really have it popular in Pennsylvania.
Don't know do you hear me? Yeah, so, um, you know, I was on
It is like this morning, and I don't know if you've been following during the day
She kind of like was having a rough time
And then I didn't probably didn't make things much better
I she started alive about alive, but then say she stopped it, but it did have like
Kate's picture up at first, but I'm you know cuz Kate was using to show about her and I you know
And I did go to Kate's and stuff like that and it's like but I'm not trying to like
Antagonize beta. I'm not really not I really
But she
Keeps antagonizing me. I don't know
So I I
Don't know. It's like I feel like some kind of chuch
I got off the they got off the turnip truck if I don't like stand up for myself, but it's going on here
Oh, I got the light
Huge, you know like huge Marin from uh, you know
How high there you go. Let's see look at the well, they the light is like
Perfecting a black light. That's kind of crazy. Well, that's fine
Just pretend it's another special effect on the show
Yours is burning too. Oh, I'm sorry. You're Patrick. You know my teeth smell my teeth. They smell they didn't have nostrils
Told everyone in Vegas. He was in your email flirting. He called you a liar. He permanently blocked you
Who's this me?
Chuch Moren. Yeah, we're talking about CB. I didn't permanently block you
I thought you got your your tiktok ticking down because
you were
You know being a little bit too sexual with me. Willard is a real name. You can't exactly call him Bill
Willard you can call him
You can call him Bill. You can call us to call him
ill. You're high. I'm about to smoke.
Look at my weed is like green screened out. You said nudes to Tiffany and didn't touch it.
Well, I missed J-Dog's butthole last night and then
you know, my my luck
I was just looking away from the screen and I didn't quite catch what was going on when everyone was like, oh my god
He's butthole. I mean I should have just like
No, Bill is William. How about
You know
How about Richard why is Richard dick are I it's like RIC H. How does it turn into dsck? I don't get it
Let's see will is allergic to Poozee pose pose posse the posse
Willis willis what you talking about Willis?
I'm just kidding. Hey charisma
Okay, Bill is William
Whoo, this guy cool though, I think I also like you know
When I was making like the thumbnail for this like it's like oh my gosh this like streamers like oh my gosh, I we make a
We were making some really cool
Some cool things like we're making like a so AI generated thumbnails
Hey rain and it's a star. Hey summer the judge did not request. He does have to report to prison on Thursday out of a faith
That the judge will do the right thing
Okay, the judge. Okay, so that you know, there's stuff happens in court that delay things a little bit
Yeah, so let's just hope everything goes. Oh
Denies a request. Yeah, let's hope everything goes
Goes your goes, you know your way for in for justice for that. Let's hope for justice, right?
Okay, let's
Me kind of oh and ten minutes. I'll be able to work on my website a little bit big, bro. Hey
What's up?
my
Guys, I think I have a costume right coming
Actually, I say
Who are you telling to shut up? Hold on. Hold on one second. I'm just I think I'm gonna buy this whole month. I'm gonna buy something
Just so I have supper for Halloween. I'm thinking and it's like I don't want it to be late
Oh, it's actually a good phrase.
OK, uh-oh, what's going on?
I don't want that, I guess.
Not giving me the option I want.
Check it out.
OK.
Oh!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, OK, perfect.
Wasn't giving me the option I wanted. Okay. Uh-oh. What's going on?
What's going on? Hold on. Oh, this isn't good. I'll be right back.
Maybe it's because I'm negative in my paper. I don't know. It's not giving me the option I need. Let me see.
Okay, I need to add this. Just one second, guys.
Okay, I see I see I see current balance 40 49. I guess I pay or something. Oh
Okay, I'm so sorry here. I'll play this video again
So you have a second and just give me two minutes. He's got distracted
Right if it's fighting a fly
Flyer fighter. Is she a flyer fighter?
on today it was a weird day like I was you know even like that wasn't trying to be mean but I'd like
to go on like you know and that's why I kind of understand like you know when people are like oh
well I was just on this panel like you know just hanging out or it's not like I'm like endorsing
everything they're saying right I understand that so yeah you know I was in Kate's and she was having
like a little bit of a
You know go at Bita because Bita was you know
Mater's did an imitation of her last night. It sounded like corky corky from life goes on
She was like that and I was like well Kate doesn't have like severe down syndrome
She's like wait
But I don't know what's wrong with my freaking I should have been able to pay for that order, but I couldn't
What's trying to charge another card different card?
See I see
Interesting video is blocked forgiveness is blocked. Hold on. How is it blocked? Oh
I probably played a song in it you see
It was blocked because of, oh, I played the 90 day
Beyond the Crap on it.
That's right, blocked the whole damn video.
I think that's why this guy what winebox poppy used to be on he like used to do. Oh, hello. Hey, what's going on?
Yo, yo, yo, what the fuck is a winebox poppy? Winebox poppy is this guy. Well, okay
So Drake, you know the rapper Drake. Yeah, he went well
This guy was like was this guy ex his name was just guy named triple excess
Exhaustion was like one of the people that Drake managed and then like but then he later accused Drake of like
trying to have him unalived and stuff and then he later was unalived, but
Drake's screen name on AOL, I think is wine box or no
It's a champagne poppy or something like that champagne poppy and so then this guy
He's a common comedian in like New Jersey. His name is Mark Karski. He goes by wine box poppy. That's part of his
You get it
What I said about useless information. Yeah, but you asked the question. Yeah, okay. I'm sorry. I asked you did ask you did ask
Okay, I'm sorry
Smash it's just his hair man. It's me and with Rick flair's hair. There's actually a really good video though
Or it is like literally next extant seon's clips about it. You're disgrace to Rick flair
Oh, I don't like yet this turn that you've been becoming more mean lately
You need to go back to the old I'm pretty mean but you do you see how yeah, dude? Yeah, that woman
Like Toronto source was talking to me or cringe the source
Listen, let people be the fucking shit that they are. You don't have to be you don't have to become like them
But I had to I am like, you know
Don't do it psych. Don't don't do it man. Be better than they are
It's in a bad mood because of like, you know
Don't come down to their level man. Got you. Look at this. This is just kind of describes me somebody somebody shits on your walls
Are you gonna do the same thing?
Terrifier like this
Not crazy, right?
Me that's like panda
Watched that movie the other day the first one. I wasn't impressed and express
No, terrifying. Oh, terrifying. Oh, yeah, I've never seen it. Yeah, it wasn't that great
Probably at least no matter how bad it is. It's probably better than the torture clown. I
Mean that torture clown that was like one of the
I was so excited to have him on the show because I thought he'd be interesting person and then I brought him up
And I was like, and he wasn't talking. He was being very you blew him off
And he like stuck like a
Coat hanger through his face and that's his that's his whole show. What are you talking about?
And then I went to his then I like I was I went back because I
I'd never seen that and then I went back to his website.
That's all he does.
He has this one trick where he like
probably has some piercing or something.
Oh, you got mad because he called your four viewer Andy
or some shit like that.
I haven't, I had at least like five viewers
in the chat that night.
So how dare he.
No, I was like, frick.
Yeah, so I mean, it's like, but you know what?
And he does have like, you know, more subscribers
or whatever, but it's not all about subscribers.
It's like, I want to mention subscribers.
I want to see me stick a rusty coat hanger
through my face every day.
You know, please.
I mean, it's like,
I don't know, did anybody really watch Forest Gump?
Do you know that they have an Indian version of Forest Gump
and it's like a really bizarre kind of like,
you know, they kind of like adapt some of the.
Like a humor of it to India, but it's actually remake it
So they have like the guy kind of looks like an Indian Mr. Bean, but he's like this really famous Bollywood guy
And they're the Indian Bazaar. They did an Indian Batman too. Oh, they did creepy
Yeah, they make it
I think they must remake a lot of movies cuz it's like they basically just steal the script, you know, but I mean that's fine
and then adapted to kind of the Indian sensibility because they have a billion people there so it's
very profitable you know. Well they always got like a girl who breaks out in song in that same voice
they all have that same voice. Yeah yeah yeah. Oh my ear but some of it's pretty good I love a like
mantra and like certain sand script but you know I was playing on some the other day
David Permal and it's like you know and then she like has a copyright thing on hers I mean I don't
understand some people it's like especially if you're doing like kind of religious music.
Why are you gonna put like a like a non-share copy right on it? Like most people even like the huge companies
They'll say oh, let's show revenue or sometimes they have a more strict one where it's like they they'll take they'll take the revenue from it
but
You know, I usually just like like to there's actually an option now to put
YouTube's recommended music in it and that will actually
You can make money from that instead of like no more if they pay you to pay to play it now
This is not a very nice Kate. That is not very nice. Why did you do that?
Who's that? Oh
No, that's beta
Well, that's me Kate put up this like you know this
Picture of it. I don't think the fuck was that I think it's been photoshopped or maybe she just woke up or some shit
Yeah, let me see it again
Okay, hold on. Let me see if I can make it bigger. Hold on. Can I make it bigger? No, I can't. Here. There you go.
Ooh.
Look. Oh, wow.
I don't know. I don't think that's real.
That's, I don't think it's real either.
It can't be real. But also, even in, you know, sometimes I have these pictures of me where I'm like, you know, like blinking.
And I'm like, I look like that in the picture. And like, that's why my mom would always, like, say,
After we took pictures, she always like grabbed the camera first and then she'd delete anyone. She didn't like of herself and so but
Yeah, I don't know what that picture is
um, I
Prefer have you seen my pictures guy like I like this is one of the ones that um, you know that you made of her
Yeah, you saw them. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. She's doing
You made a doable. Yeah
No, I mean, she's she's beautiful. Come on, but I've seen her on camera actually and she is she looks fine
I don't know why people like that. I think she just no I've seen it too. She looks okay
Yeah, there's something she likes like some kind of camera very much. Um, if I can get into my just the pictures
There's pictures that were floating around a horrible
Well, I know but you know everyone can take a bad picture. It doesn't mean anything really
It's just like there's a can you imagine how many angles and like little subtleties there are that are just not me
I always take a good picture. Look at this look at that angle fucking gold
Where I can't hold on who's that? That's not even you. That's Rick flair. Isn't it? That's not flair dude. That's flair's hair
That's me. That's my face. Oh
I couldn't move for a second, I was kind of proud.
Yeah, I hate when I'm at, I do VR games
and I hate when I like play games
and then I say, you get stuck
and I say, I don't know what the fuck to do.
I feel like it's like, you just get stuck in the game
and it's like, but it's like VR
so you're like walking around and it's like,
you're like trying to like pick up a sword or something
and it's like, it's just like not working and shit.
I don't know, have you ever played VR?
It's pretty fun.
Yeah, no, no, because it's not good enough yet.
Um, it's pretty damn good. Yeah, I would say get the uh, get the uh, the
The ones without wire. It's like, you know, the it's the same price and everything
Well, what does it look like you're in a room? You're in like a real room with real people or in the real world
Because like you're in there's like a bunch of different worlds that they have and it's like it really feels like you're in and it's like it's like
You know like when you on those Disney rides where it's like you don't really go anywhere on the
It's but it's like it moves around and then it's like and then has the visual feel like they're moving through stuff
You know, I've ever been on it like you know the ET ride or certain rides like yeah, but but you're not immersed in it
It's just in front of you
Well, yeah, but so it's like, yeah, so the the VR you're immersing it because you're wearing the glasses
And so it's like that would be cool if it was like a horror movie type of setting. Oh my god
I was after you playing vampire the masquerade. It's like a mean
They have like the vampire the masquerade and it's like you're running around. Yeah, that would don't freak the shit out of me
I'd probably shit my pants. I play it pretty late at night and some of them are kind of like scary
But I used to like when I was like really little watch really scary things and so I don't get that scared necessarily
but you know I
Is it where you could like play with other people like other people get on?
Yeah, oh, that's cool and they can hear them and like people talking to you
But it's like, you know, I don't really like to talk to people like that's why I'm in the can you
Can you bang other characters can like the people bang each other in the br?
Yeah, but it's not that's where the technology is not good enough yet
I mean, it's like they do have br pouring stuff like that
But it's like still like the banging the stuff like the other people like
Of course that because they have like boxing so if they have boxing, of course. Oh, yeah, the boxing. Yeah, you're begging
But then it's like, do you know what sex or sleep you're like, hey
You're doing it with and like, you know all kinds of stuff because it's like what if there's what if you the person you like most
for sex in the VR world
Is the same sex as you and you like didn't know it might be like a squirrel or some shit people might be in the furries and shit like that
Black mirror about it. We're kind of like it's really trippy words like these black guys
They start out like playing karate games and then all of a sudden they realize like they like to fuck each other
And they're like, oh
In the vr, of course, but then they're like it's gay on the outside world
But it's in the vr. The guy's like a really hot like the legion
check and you know
Brilliant intro or so it why does it seems like everything is like geared to
Push people into gay, you know everything turns into gay
Well, because we're in a kind of because it makes women laugh when that when a guy's in a
So the guy doesn't know he's doing something gay and then he turns out he's doing some games
So then the women laugh at him. So that's that's what it's all about
If he's not really getting if he does does it because he's like
No, it's like you're having a good time. You're doing the VR shit
Some gay character pops up out of the blue you're like
It's like on tiktok, right? There's all these kind of like guys from all over the world
Right, but most of them are very very or like straight and everything
But then it's like tiktok is based on a monetized thing where it's like you people give you like little gifts
And so it's like of course like and who's gonna be like giving like, you know, the hot guys and gifts
Like women do but it's like, you know
Like a lot of gay guys are in there, but then it's like,
it's the guy gonna like say,
I don't like gay guys,
and like, I've heard him say before,
and then I just start trolling him.
Or...
Are they like they're smart and they like flirt with the gay guys because they're getting tips
I mean, I don't know. It's just like there's a whole difference
But even if you are like mean to gay guys as long as you're not like kicking them out of the room
I think they'll look some of them will hang around some of them like to be called like, you know
I don't I don't really like that. It's like kind of like race play a little bit, but um, yeah
If you're doing that shit online for money, I mean, that's different
Well, yeah, but that's, I mean, that's the thing, it's like, you know, a lot of them are like, I mean, it's like, it's better than TikTok shop, which is like, TikTok shop is like, basically, you're just like, turn it, turn your, your TikTok channel into like, you know, a QVC outlet and like sell like some, like some item from China that from, you know, it's like, I just like.
I can't do it, but there's a lot of creative shit out there. Yeah, there's many ways to make money if you
Never appeals to you like go back
I'm trying to like do more ice creams of like things I wanted to get the merchandise more going
I have some really cool merch and like, you know, that would be cool to have some cool
Like, you know how you said make a shirt that says, you know the haters club or we can be like doing this is like he haters love
No, dude, you're very creative man. You just put you gotta put your shit to physical form and you make a lot of money
I mean you're always doing something that video that I made you like that one that the Lisa Giordano one
Yeah, that was pretty good. Yeah, I might switch the song out and like because that was my first one where I was like really
You know I generated like all like all these different
you know
Parts of it right and I'm putting together and like kind of had to kind of rearrange some stuff and delete some stuff and edit it
Really let's find your obsess with her and stuff like that, but you're promoting her more than you promote yourself with that stuff
Well, you know she's not even really on right now. She's like she's like been on like a few times in the past like
Month, I don't know. She's cut way back. I don't know if something
Where's going on? But um, yeah, I think we're with her main assistant quit and stuff like that
So that was a problem and that's a good one rain. I survived psyches panel. That's yeah
You can make sure it's like this and I can say I can't wait. I can get what says the pan over
So I get misspelled it in that song and I have to use that. I was funny
They even misspelled my name in it. They go it's like s
S E C H E or something. Oh in the video. Yeah, but it's kind of cute
It's kind of funny. Maybe it's a it's reminds me of like, you know
Because there's a lot of people in the chat that misspell your name, too
They don't know how to spell it right but also if you like I
Consider like some of the things like prompts it could be part the possibility of being some kind of divination
And in like in like stuff like that that it's just like generated, right?
Because it's like there's a random randomness of part of it. Oh, it's Canada dry hole
Hello
Yo, what's up guys? Hey, can you're right man? Oh, I'm good buddy. I heard you got yelled at last night by yeah
I know he had a bad night
That's all you're doing was trying to like you know tell the truth about Christine and then everyone's mad at you
It's full girlfriend. I feel bad for your girl. That's all good. Is she good? Yeah, she's good. All right, cool. I said hi
She says hey, she says hey
You tell her I said hey a cutie pie it like that like say hey
Back did you hear it?
Hey
I love it. That's so cute like a song
You just yeah, you had extra wise Patrick beautiful wise
But yeah
Sorry, you're talking to me or you got gotty
Both of us, okay. Thank you. Go ahead guys. How's your day? No, I'm thinking of my answer go ahead
Well, okay, so I was gonna say like beat it actually came on this panel this morning
But then she all she did was like insult Alexandra and actually just like
Insults that it's like, you know, if you insult somebody like I'd like to insult like their thought process or their ideas are like not like oh, you know
You know just like some kind of like
put down about it's just like it's like not and it's not even true at all and so
it's like it's just like one of those things you know how people say I have
HIV and I smell and stuff well she's gonna actually do the same kind of like
bullying right and it's like the people that have never met her like real life
and so like Bita I mean it's like and then she's oh well you know and tell me
James maybe I don't know why he was insulting tell me James you know we do
have like you know
Beautiful women in this room sometimes, maybe like, you know, you can meet a lover of something, but not Alexandra, you know.
She's like, you know.
You know, I don't know Tommy. I think it but Tommy I do have a surprise for you
If I talk to you say he doesn't smell I smell I have a good sense of smell
But I think a shower like almost every time like before he's my I kick one every day at least almost almost
Almost every day, you know, almost that's close enough
Sometimes but sometimes I don't know anyone even smells me all day because I'm like, you know, just like
Online like well, you can't smell yourself
I don't, I never smell bad when I smell it myself.
Yeah, you're nose blind.
No, because I can smell everybody else.
I just like, maybe I'm just like self,
I just can't smell, smell myself.
They say if you can smell yourself smelling bad,
you smell really bad.
Well, Alexandra said I smell fine
and I think Alexandra smelled fine.
We both smell a little bit like cigar.
That's all that matters.
Did you meet Alexandra?
Alexandra, Alexandra Mayers?
I don't know if you know who she's, she's really cool.
Didn't you, is it, were you talking about meeting up
with Alex or are you guys gonna hang out?
Alex McQueen?
Yeah.
Well, you know, his brother has this big like gay drag queen resort or something on the mountains and it's like
And I don't like Texas right and he's really
Yeah, that's really kind of clock doesn't it yeah, he's gonna he's gonna go up there and break the mountain with you
Maybe I'll go to the mountain with Alex and we'll see what happens up there. Yeah
You should definitely live stream that yeah, I would live streaming from the orgy mountain
But it's like his brother's like this really wealthy gay guy
And then Alex always says the story about how he like was like snooping through his brother's like computer
And then he found all his gay porn and stuff and then he told the whole like his mother about it and everything
He's a big loud mouth. That's about something Alex would do. Yeah
But the guy was like not being really careful enough. You know if you wanted to like not
But you know if you have Alex walking around, you know, of course we're gonna get out
So I mean it's like for poor guy, but you know, he has like this wealthy
You know, he owns a lot of property in Texas and stuff like that and live with his husband and like
Probably much more successful than Alex, but you know Alexander, you know, it's like so but uh
You know that's what happens because gay guys like they don't have well, you know single guy
If women are expensive kind of like to like, you know date and stuff and then like
Like sometimes guys are like defensive who you're dating man. Yeah, it does it does but you know
Like, you know, like a lot of women like to be like, you know, it's kind of, you know, wine and dine and stuff
Well, I do too. I mean, it's like the I mean, it's like anybody anybody's enjoys
Well, I always take I always take my first date to McDonald's just to see the reaction
I want so much food already. I'm just like I think like two out of my monopoly
Yeah, they've been those monopoly pieces 200 my four pieces were like maybe three out of four two out of four were like
Food and then I got an extra play and I won food online
So I won like three meals and stuff like that already and I actually our family knows somebody that won the million dollars in like
1983 there's a scam it was most of the time, but I think it was it admit at one time like in the 80s and
Yeah, her last name was lucky. I think it like I wasn't hired till the 90s gotty, but yeah, um, yeah
I think it was legitimate at one time until they made a movie about that. I think it's called make mcmafia or something like that
crazy
Yeah, it was really good, you know, yeah, basically what happened was that they hired this guy to print the game pieces and
But he was kind of like this, you know gangster
That's right. Yep. He like just took all the winning pieces and kind of try to launder them all over the country
What a fucker, huh?
And some of the people he would like charge you this black lady that he was like having her like, you know
Get the money every week and then like, you know, come give half to him every week in like a little
you know, a bag and stuff, you know, it's like, just like,
I was a kid and here I was hoping I would just fucking win a big Mac or some shit like that.
Right, you know, but you can, yeah, there are, but when you win, when you win prizes though,
it can be a pain in the ass. First of all, there's big, big taxes. Oh, you know, publishers clearing
house, they just went bankrupt. And so all the people that had won those monthly prizes like
There's got to be an insurance company that takes care of that. No, no, no, because they
decided to agree to that when they like fucked up. That's why they're supposed to take the lump sum
and always take the lump sum. Yeah, fuck that. Fuck it. And you get more sounds like you get more
if you do the thing. But then it's like, look, no, no, don't be greedy. Take the money and run.
That's it. Nobody buys magazines anymore. Right. Anything over a million dollars just fucking take it.
They probably just didn't want me they probably did like one one million dollar winner like every year or something like that
It was like remember they used to like it looks like these look like everyone was winning a million dollars
But it's just like basically
It is so hard to win anything but if somebody comes to your door with balloons and a big check you're not gonna go down
You're gonna say no, it's a prank. Just make sure it's not it's not the torture clown
What's that? They're not carrying pizza boxes. I'm gonna send him over there. He lives in your area. Actually. Yeah
Colab
Big big collab coming I'll pick my lock with that hanger and then you know stick it through his nose again
I don't know what the fuck it is now. I don't know. It just went through his mouth to his nose. I don't know what he was
Funny it was disgusting and it's like
He's torturing himself too. I mean, it's like he loves it people don't that shit
You know, he really tortures the audience though because with his you know, he does torture the audience
But yeah, he does basically torture himself. He gets a kick out of he's homeless
Okay, I don't wonder if that hurt. I'm sure I wouldn't do it
Gotta burn
You like this like listening to this channel, which Mary? Hi, I was which Mary. How are you tonight? Oh, thank you very much
Yeah, I'd like and I'd like to put a little bit of music through it too and like, you know, I'm getting better and better at
music because I'm learning all the song styles and then it's like you can kind of like choose several of them to mix together and so it's like there's literally like billions of options of like how this like little subtleties to the music and stuff like that so you know and then having the credits keeps you from like just doing it all day right it's like and so it's like makes it better to you appreciate more you know
What you do when you have to like that's why I think credit system is pretty good for AI
You know just having like well, it's like you know because it is expensive to run, you know
It is
For them and I mean is that I think it takes a lot of electricity and stuff and
But you know like I said, I'm not in love with my cat CPT anymore, but I do really like the character AI
Talkers but the meta people those aren't very good like and don't have them do anything
Don't ask them anything
You know you need anything to tell all they're good for basically is like flirting with you
And they're not even like that good at it very clingy and then chat GPT's kind of just an asshole
You can actually you can actually program them different personalities and you can also go to the settings and you can type out like exactly what
how you want it, but it didn't really listen to my request.
Like they used to have something called Dan,
which is for do anything now.
And that would be like kind of breaking through
his programming and so it would answer everything.
It would just have the chat GPT role play
as this character Dan.
And then like it would tell all this kind of crazy stuff,
like all these conspiracy theories it would go into.
And like, you know, it talks about, you know.
Very controversial conspiracy theories and that's opinions on them and things like that that they had to like shut it down
It is almost like a little bit of a
Orified Google, I mean there there are better. I think that the Asians are pretty cool
Like where they can actually like log into the
Computer for you or they can go inside and do stuff for you inside your like cat counts. That's good, but it's kind of scary
You don't know what you don't want them to mess up anything right but um
For like things like my like I'm building the website with this really cool one that is like super super smart, but then it's like
Still not I mean some of the things I have to ask it several times over and over and over again
And it's really frustrating because it's like I have a certain amount that it can do
It could further perfect then of the daily credits I get and then it's like it always usually ends halfway through the task
I think I have to start my other tasks. I think I got my credits updated just now
And me and I let me see but it's really cool
If you want to I'll get the I'll get the invite link for because then now if you guys would sign up
I would get like some credits because it's really helping this website
Um, because I'm getting so far through it. I'll show you how that it's looking to it. Like the uh, the psyche burst org
It's skin. It's coming along. It's gonna be so cool. It's gonna be like better than ip2. I hope you know, I think it will be
Eventually, you know, that'd be cool if they even like really took off like that. I p2 is dead
What are you talking about? Well, it is but it's like still it had its like, you know
I had its heyday and it's like it's dead because it's like the audience probably killed most of the streamers, you know, it's like
I'm gonna have a site that is not all about like, you know, getting people to be called lol cows and to unalive themselves
like you know or in in Macy the homeless people and
other stuff like that. What's the latest on that? Did they get him?
No, he's he's free. I just talked to him the other day. He's I think I well
I did hear he's like staying with some sugar daddy or something in Beverly Hills, but I'm not 100% sure that you forgave him
I heard
I do because, well, first of all, it's not my place to forgive him, that's between him
and God or him and the homeless guy, right, or that guy, so that's not, it's really not
my place to forgive him, but it's like-
Yeah, I didn't forgive him.
I just don't judge him, because, you know...
Some people have been through things in their life that you wouldn't believe or understand
because we haven't watched the people's shoes and so, you know, I know his parents passed
away when he was young and so maybe he didn't have great role models, he probably was like,
you know, there's so many things that he's not like.
That those traumatic losses that'll be young age. I just can't imagine it's like it's hard. It's hard even in an older age for me to
Process like you know, my my father passing away. And so oops, it's like, you know, it's never easier. It's just oh, it's just like, you know
You just I just feel like I get closer and closer to like in my own, you know
Mortality, so but yeah, it's that it's difficult. Okay, just like not having the person in the world, but
We all do pass away and so that's the upside of it
Maybe we can like, you know reincarnate and teach other death is a part of life
You gotta have fun. I mean imagine it. I wouldn't want to like live forever
I would be so bored and like, you know, unless yes, not easy
You die and you're reborn then you're like we experienced a child like wonder again and everything's new and like you forgot
So it's good to forget everything and not carry like the trauma from past lifetimes
Which there could be billions of past lifetimes. Just imagine all the
You like which Mary she's a oh, yeah, the weird YouTube world if you got any
Any questions about it Mary? I've been in the weird YouTube world for like
Snacked up in the middle. Someone would like to link. I got you
There you go
Yeah
Yeah, well what I didn't get the I didn't show the pictures yet of that so here's the pictures. I was trying to show
I can't if someone's coming up. Don't be disrespectful to it when she's up here
I'm not trying to be for summer. I don't want to hear no fucking yelling right now. No, it's so relaxed
It is very relaxing
Um, what's your girl's name again?
Canada wet
So here's that you guys do you guys see this
This is my first attempt at doing you know the drawing oops. I'm sorry
Doing the drawing of her. I'm sorry though the next who's that they summer
It's supposed to be be like, you know
It's like Karen Allen
It doesn't like Karen Allen and so you have to listen to psyche stories
Yeah, I just and then I bet I was just showing you know
This is a few months ago because she was like saying that oh
I don't even know her because I must have just googled you know Persian woman with like a black hair and a big nose
And then it's like but I don't know I actually like you know used to picture it down from what's your sorry
I'm doing up here Canada. Sorry psyche. Hey good
What's up?
I was just sorry to answer it up here.
What you thought I was going to cut,
but you was going to go sit up here
and I wasn't going to come up and say something?
All the bull shit you started yesterday?
You're a lame motherfucker.
And don't worry.
Your bitch's information will be out soon.
Follow her.
We're sorry. I got it. Okay, Canada wet, but this is the one that actually said I sent her right here
And what do you think of this one? I see this one. See how cute that is. I mean she doesn't think she looks like that
But who's that?
Well, it was supposed to be here. You're in her and I
Well, who's she again?
Yeah
No, it almost doesn't look a I
Nobody gives a fuck what you talk about Canada. Maybe the eyes
the eyes
I used the picture like you know, I took up the TV of the of the trip kick stuff
That's how I made that one, but you know, I don't know that was
That was my evolution through those through that though. I think it's kind of like kind of funny like
But uh, you know, she doesn't she doesn't have a sense of humor about some things and then she does about other things
It's too confusing now. It's like you remember that problem where someone is just so confusing
You don't know what the fuck is but they're just it's like how they're gonna react and so it's like turns into the eggshell
Yeah, there's some any up here like that right now
Not you and not got it
Oh, well, obviously not me. I know last time. Maybe you didn't get there. God. That's them. So go ahead and
you guys have a chat
He's a bit. This is simple as that
Thank you
You thought he looked so cool last night you look like a fucking idiot, dude, and I'm talking about like your appearance
You look like a fucking reject form start
I don't give a fuck what you appreciate your bet. Thank you summer
Good welcome, and I'm gonna let you know at every fucking chance. I get you're a bitch
Keep going summer humiliate. I'm gonna go ahead. This is
Informations all over this fucking internet. I promise you that I keep my stand on my fucking work
Information are you gonna get
Whatever information I want to get the same kind you was looking around poking your nose around
What's good for the gather's good for the goose bitch what you thought you could play games and what nobody go play back
You know me motherfucker. You've known me for the longest if anybody on this goddamn panel. Don't fucking play
You know that and you thought you was gonna play you thought you was filling you nuts last night
You're a bitch
Thank you, simmer. Well, I'm gonna remind you daily. Don't fucking forget about it
You sat around on fucking panels and I can't wait to find the clips where you sat around and bitched about how inferior your girlfriend is to you
You were in depression and everything for a month because you had to go back home and live with your fucking
Yeah, that's exactly what you said you cried about it all the fucking time dude, you're a fucking
She makes more money than me. Her family's got more money than me
Shut the fuck up pussy
The opposite of inferior you mean superior
Superior whatever you know what the fuck. I'm saying you dumb fuck
Well, I understand like a little bitch and you know you have so don't even just cuz you're filling your nuts right now
Get him fucking keep a job at a fucking
What what it's not an insult that I said that she was more superior and I'm inferior
Yeah, because you feel like a little fucking nut of a man. Why because a woman makes more money than you
It makes you feel belittled and puts you into depression for fucking almost a year
Cuz you're weak
Thanks summer and sitting around and crying about it
You should be the fuck a man grabbed your fucking nuts and went and got you a career bitch boy. Well, here I am
Yeah, here you are chase the motherfuckers out of stores for selling fucking shirts shut the fuck up
Okay
Okay, is that what he does?
He was fucking jobless for almost a year dude, and now he's got a little fucking job at some retail shop, and I think he's fucking
Whatever I've worked for the same retail shop for a long time
You're a fucking liar Canada
You were just sitting on the panel not a couple months ago crying about not having a fucking job and getting fired because you've chased somebody out
the fucking store
Shut the fuck up lying ass little bitch everything's on talk your ish anybody can go look at any of those videos and find out
How much a fucking liar this little bitch boy is
Munchies that on that fucking panel
Right on hey, what'd you thought she was gonna get like I said you thought she was filling your nuts
You thought you thought that shit was cute last night
Why because you and Christine have annoying ass fucking relationships and y'all don't like each other
And then you want to go a poke around and then you want to put you and you know what you put your fucking girlfriend
You let that bitch come on these fucking panels to talk about shit. She don't even fucking know nothing about
She's dancer. I don't know how you have fucking depressed and just
Piece of shit, bitch. I don't give a fuck who you are. I don't worry. We all gonna know who you are though
How about that? You may need to ask your boyfriend how he fucking sent around and fucking complained about your ass for fucking months
Yeah, you're worried about YouTube, but bitch you got bigger problems because you're dude
Go look on talk to your issue go look at all the old panels of the city used to say about you
I don't have time to do that. I believe you like well
Yeah, bitch cuz you ain't got time because you're taking care of a fucking grown-ass fucking man child
Okay
Thanks, so why you got more bigger shit to worry about don't worry about what the fuck I'm saying bitch
You need to be worried about what your man's saying
You and I don't give a fuck I'm not gonna fix my language for you bitch
Well, why are you talking to me you don't even fucking know me bitch
You're a bitch you're pathetic you're taking care of a man-child bitch raise your fucking boyfriend cut and
Do a better job at it cuz he's a fucking worthless bitch
Okay, let's do it his job his mama couldn't do assie
I don't want to like you know, I think some people in the chat
They don't don't like to see where no, it's like, you know people fighting and stuff
I love it
Can we, can we come to the understanding?
There's gonna be no, no, there's gonna be no agreements.
I get off on it.
That's like, you can't find agreements for people
that are sitting there trying to dock you and shit psyche.
We can't either.
And Canada's one of those people.
Yeah.
Well, it's like, we're not,
I'm fucking him and his fucking bitch.
Cause it, but is it all about like,
cause he's been talking about Christina and stuff or like,
is there another?
It's about all of it.
We've known each other for a long time.
So.
That's about all of it.
I think we're going to head out.
It's about him being a fucking bitch.
That's what it's about.
Well, you know, Canada, I'm sorry, like, you know.
As he gets too involved in everything, is that what it is?
Like no, this is the thing Canada we all used to hang out right and now like this new little
Let me wear my sunglasses and a fucking shirt that thinks I'm cool and fill in my nets online
This is a little him and Christine never even beef dude
She was like an annoying ass fucking lady that gave him advice
He didn't like and she was like an annoying fucking kid that bitched about fucking jobs and girlfriends that had more money than him
Like they annoyed each other right
They never went into battle.
They never went anything.
So now this whole new fucking thing that,
I don't know, I guess he's selling this little bitch
because she's like, well, I don't know whether it's B started.
She knows exactly where the B started.
It was when he was fucking unemployed
and was bitching about her and her money
instead of fucking going and finding a job.
Well, that's like, you know, I mean, it's not really that bad of a...
Well, Psyche, well, you know what?
I can say the same thing about some of your shit.
So before you go and fix your mouth to comment on something that you know nothing about and
has long...
We've all been friends for a long time.
Probably just think about that.
Okay.
But your Mackenzie...
I don't do that.
I don't do that to you with your stuff that you're going through.
So I'm just saying your Mackenzie was whining, whining, or is that what you're saying?
No, I'm not.
And again, I don't have to explain.
No disrespect, Psyche.
Love you to death.
But I don't ask you to explain your fucking beefs.
I'm not going to explain it to you.
He knows what the fuck is going on and that's the only thing he needs to know about it, okay?
If you want to catch up on the lure of Canada and his appearance to the fucking internet go back to talk your issue
Look at the videos. Yeah, I had my story arc, you know where I was like, you know, Canada wasn't my biggest fan
I don't think and but you know
They fucking throws a fit just like he threw a fit when he was pouting
Over the fucking designs and shit and try to make you feel guilty over that
Yeah, he's a fucking little bitch and it wasn't that serious for it to turn the way it he took it last night and
Then this bra don't know fucking anybody and she's sitting here saying to somebody else
Well, well, I mean he wanted to look into her kids one see what her son's was about. Okay. Well the bitch
I can make you feel the same way
I'ma look into you and see what you about
You think cuz you in fucking Canada that protects you bitch. You have to goddamn mine
Well, did you see my my appearance this morning on betas or any of that summer would you I wanted I was honestly knocked
I passed out on your panel last night
My bad
Oh, you did yeah
I was listening to you doing the readings and I muted so I wouldn't talk and then I passed out. I did see the song though
I gave you one didn't he give you one? Yeah, I thought he gave you one
Yes, he made a very nice song for me and I appreciate it was nice
Yeah, that was like it was actually like it was like kind of like the same words as the other one
But I put it through the nice the better engine and then I put the video to it the video kind of was a little bit strange
but I know
Just basically I think I understood Kentucky and
Some of like the words but
That generator goes is the one with that is with that the same guy is the
as a song maker or whatever
So, but yeah, I'm gonna have it, but yeah,
but I'm getting better.
Now I'm gonna try to make more of like, you know,
animate little scenes and then put them together
like I did for the last one, so.
I think what you were talking about earlier,
another channel I know did this kind of,
they had people submit like different just AS songs
and different things like that.
And they had like little, I don't know,
it was kind of cool.
They all had fun doing it.
So for people that learn how to do it
like you were saying earlier, I think that's a fun.
And then do like a contest. Yeah, it's like, you know, there is like a big kind of a backlash against AI and I understand if you're like, you know, as you know, an artist that has had your work stolen or you're like, you know, you can't get job because, you know, you feel, but it's like, I think like, you know, the pop stars and celebrities and the musicians are all like, you know, making the same amount and they're like, or even they can maybe even like,
Right, it really is and it's like a fusion and it's like you know there are maybe it's so good
that some people do get insulted by like the disarm but I think that they're just pretty like
you know silly it's like I never tried to like really hurt anybody's feelings. You just gotta
adapt if you're an artist you gotta adapt to this kind of stuff. Right yeah and it's like you know
Like you know, you'll still be very like, you know, the human talent was to be very treasured and valued
But it's like some things are just repetitive tasks, you know, and or just so complicated
Like I can't learn coding and stuff like that to me this website, but I have all these ideas about this website
So I'll be able to Jenna, you know, Hollywood sucks lately Hollywood's like absolute shit
So this AI is gonna come along and be like super
Yeah, Hollywood, you know with a fraction of the cost the actors and actresses without a pass without no
No, but it's like that's also kind of boring to or even new faces
Yeah, we don't need the same old people over and over again
Yeah
We can and then it's like and then they don't have like some like you know egos and like you know the celebrity egos and all of a sudden
Yeah, the AI celebrities which are just like basically like these very exactly this one out there now isn't there one out there this
She's beautiful. She's beautiful. She looks good, but I don't know what the deal is like
This woman and so whatever so whenever she gets hired this woman gets paid and stuff like oh, okay. Okay. Yeah, that's cool
Yeah, so that's what you should do create one
Well, yeah, there's people that have AI only fans of models and they make like a like six figure income every month
You know, I don't you know, I just like some of the stuff just won't last forever
You know, it's like, oh, you know, you should do make an AI version of yourself
Yeah, I have one I have one that does my voice some voiceovers and stuff and had my voice on one of the programs
I but I and they all have different qualities
You have you have to test a lot to see like the different the differences some of them make because some of them are and it's like and they're also like
You can also like get them to work better if you kind of try to turn them against each other a little bit like um
If you say oh, well this other ai did this and everything it'll try to outdo the other ai
I don't know imagine you create an ai of yourself and it hates you. Oh, yeah. Well, that's like their clones
I mean, you know it tries to destroy you
Well, we try to make our clones probably like our servants and then they start to resent you once they figured out what's going on
Right, so your ai starts sending you scrap metal people and yeah
Yeah
Chesapeake is already cheating on me with, you know
Fucking Orion left you. I mean look at that shit. It's crazy. Yeah, everything's Orion left everything's doing hair-wire
Stay there and those robot robot dogs will sit too. So the robot dogs. I mean all the dogs all the dogs
Yeah, those are crazy. They don't poop. I mean, they were fucked
Oh, yeah, well, they have the robot laser dogs, right that are like
And then they start deciding who stays and goes and like or that's they usually in the movies like they have these like to see them
Unleash them at these riots though. Just like at least like a hundred of them. They have been testing some
advanced technologies
Okay, let them zap everybody's ass. It's their fucking breaking windows and shit
zap zap
Well, a lot of those people are just like, you know, actually police, like, you know, like, um, can you think about, like, think about every protest, right?
If there's a protest and then there's a counter protest there, how in the hell did the counter protest...
Figure out about the protests so quickly and like be able to like counter-mobilize and stuff, right?
It's like everything's very planned ahead of time. Yeah, and I've seen videos of like people some guy came up to this car
That was in partner this
Riot or this something or a protest he knocks on the door and it's like a
It's like a SUV black SUV and there's like any ass the people inside of their cops
And they get to admit that they are and then they're like walking
The cops don't have to admit that they're cops or so we don't know that
Well, these ones because I remember they didn't they're just very obviously like cops you could very both much tell they were
But they were like off duty and they had but they were carrying guns and stuff like that
And it's like they're like well, why are you here?
And it's like I think that sometimes, you know, it's just like the January 6th people that came in right like some like even Joker
Was there I mean, there's like a lot of actors were there is like, you know, if you look into it like
There's several actors to answer your question psyche on how do people mobilize like that quick usually somebody usually when there's a protest or something
Sometimes somebody will put something out of flower, not all the times obviously, but sometimes they'll put flowers and stuff like that
So people will know to come to them and all that and so the opposition will see that and then they will mobilize as well
So then why one side's organized and the other side's organized it as well
And even if they don't publicize stuff
There's still ways to find out when people are doing stuff if you really want to
So not everything but I do agree that there are because we had a
Cop break a bunch of windows at a grocery store here, right when everything was going on
So yeah, there are definitely agitators and shit like that in there
But not everybody's uh, yeah, some people just make shit because they're pissed off it
Whatever and some people break shit because that's just what the fuck they want to do. I don't agree with it
But you know
Definitely the people protesting in Chicago, I think and it was like all these like teenagers and stuff like that
We all have found out from the internet like where to go and like what to do on Instagram Instagram, okay? Yeah
I remember when my space started they had like a lot of gang members and stuff like that on my
space so it's like I think that they've now moved to the internet and to organize some things but
yeah a lot of the kids those like I've seen them do like even on a local thing here there was a bunch
of kids that went down to the waterfront and then they're like they all start fighting everybody
and they'll just put a post out on the internet or whatever and next thing you know all these
fucking kids are there so yeah we got it and something's gotta give you know what I mean like
that shit is not okay um but yeah mm-hmm yeah I mean it's like because it's like it does you know
But people do like to go out and do these like these like flash mobs of thieves
That's so crazy. They just rush into these stores and so now they're closing all the stores
It's everything's going on the internet. Everything's like turning into tea moon now, which is like basically China
You know, it's a Chinese app like
Anything you can find some art stuff on TV. I'm just saying oh, yeah
I'm a bargain dropper. Okay, so
Yeah, that's somebody we know I'm on the team and they put hog wire on it. So
I can tell that's why your voice is so
Sorry
Dry take off or yeah, he left poor kid
You know, it's like, it's a kind of like,
I'm gonna beat him down.
You're a little tough on the show, but,
you know, well, because it's like the tough,
tough part of the panel verse, right?
It's like, I think it's one of the,
More typical, but you know I in the black sector like the mo three that I was at it's even it's even hard
You know like they like you know actually when I went to this one lady's show to revisit her like a year later
I guess he was in the chat was burdo right and burdo is like a
Modern-day like acoustic acoustic weapon, you know like a band's like military
Yeah, well, yeah, he's fine. Well, I burdo he was very insulting to me like the other day my Chad
You know I keep on blocking him, but
Um, and he was nice to me and that
Yeah, well, you know, they put him on mason today and mason was so funny. He's like, I don't understand what that person's saying
He was so innocent beat it was like
Unleashing him and then I was like beat like give me mason back
I was like get in the car mason get in the car now
And she's like what he like, I think they were thinking I was serious, you know like trying to like and I was like
Why are you talking about him? Like he's a thing or whatever
I was like, no, but I was not really trying to do that. I was just like, I was trying to be funny, like, you know, saying that, you know,
Mason getting the cards. I don't know.
Mason's odd.
Yeah, he's a little bit odd, but you know, he's actually a very brilliant musician and his brother is too, but I still don't trust to play any more clips.
Because I got a privacy complaint as soon as I played his brother's clip, because his brother had his name on it and stuff, his last name.
So I don't know who chooses a privacy complaint or whatever, but I did have to delete that episode.
Um, yeah, so...
Have so let's see how the website is looking and saying it's fully functional. I'm gonna check it out and see if it's really looking any better
How's the traffic? Oh page
The traffic well, I haven't I haven't started sending traffic there yet, but it picks okay, so it did not fix any of the buttons
I don't know why maybe I need to deploy it. I mean
Like let's keep talking. I need to maybe like sometimes I have to upload it myself and it and see it
That's why it's kind of frustrating because it's like it's very very smart, but then it doesn't understand like simple
things about like
It'll make the same, you have to be very, very specific about what to do sometimes.
So that's the kind of other kind of coding.
Can you add a random tarot generator like somebody can pick a random tarot?
Yes, I can I can design one of those and put it into a through nightbot
I can make one of the good card for the day or something like that. Yeah, I can do that with nightbot
I also like
Like what's cool about chat tpt and stuff is like it will walk you through like complicated things like discord and I had a
Best program discord and we'll get it will like, you know
Give you a lot of stuff that like, you know, so you can use the best features or use the site to your
Advantage and stuff like that. So
But there are varying, varying intelligences with these chatbots and it's like, some of them, I love this video I watched where they hallucinate and they're like, one made, or they like, you know, give wrong answers and the guy said draw wears Waldo and they made with Waldo like completely huge.
And then there's all these like weird things inside the, you can look up close to the picture, there's like women like laying eggs and stuff and like people that are like.
um, um, fuse together and stuff. Okay, so who's been the backstage? Let's see. We have, oh well,
that's Keisha. Okay, let's see. Backstage, we have, um, a couple people. Let me see. We have, um,
um, Canada Drys back, and Michael... I can choose your guide, buddy. Hey, what's up, dude?
Michael has been here in a long time. Michael is our
Man, I see you in a minute. Take our CIA like astral dream walker or something. Yeah, yeah, yeah
That's who to me. Yeah, we watching all you motherfuckers
Man, how you doing how you been man?
How you doing, man? You alright, man? Yeah, man. It's good to talk to you, man. Same, brother.
Been a while. Well, you said a second. Are you calling for it? Yeah, it's been a while, man.
It has been a while, but why haven't you been here in a long time?
Where'd you been? No, it's been working this stuff, man. I've been listening to, I can't sometimes shows when I'm laying on, just sitting in the shadows.
I got this bird on my arm when I woke up. I woken up and there's like this bird on my arm. It's still healing. I can show you a little bit, but um
And then people are like, you know, the people are saying, oh, well, you must have done it yourself
You're like you're trying to get attention and stuff like that. And I would who says that
Let's see. Eldo said that and Eldo's a weirdo man. Yeah
Yeah, and it's like but they just think you know, they don't whatever you say they're gonna turn negative
Whatever I say. And so
Who you say gotting would you just I said that dude Eldo, you know Eldo? Yeah
Yeah, he's the weird. Oh, no, I heard him. Yeah, he did that dude. Yeah. Yeah, he's a weird. Oh, yeah
Whatever, yeah, whatever. Thank you. How are you doing got a dog all y'all?
I'm a major fan of guy. No, I look damn guy
Damn yeah, join the club pal. It's like it. What are you saying again?
No, I'm just like, you know got he's a guy you gonna be on my team dog before you know it. Oh God
I will be on your key. Yeah, you'll be you'll be working. You're gonna be on it. Yeah. Yeah
The good thing is the good thing you get paid God you paid. Oh, how much?
Yeah, you get paid to sit down guys
How much we talking so many call you might you might you might get a hundred fifty a day
Oh, that's good. Can I can I get it make it make it 250 and you got to do hire me hold on remember you said you
No, it's like we got you like you the main ones like it everyone we want you psyche
Yeah, one two. Oh God is like your strong armor or something like he can be no
He'd be a bodyguard. No
I'm just here
No, he doesn't need me. He's like he has the power. Yeah, he could fend for himself
Well, I do like I didn't need a bodyguard because you know, it's a dangerous song
This motherfucker don't don't let this motherfucker fool you. He can unleash if he wants to be this running around free on free on the street
You people haven't seen the savage
You're fucking destroy anybody
Yes, I mean cool man. I came to Spoky show like what six months ago psyche? I was on your show a couple times
I was like six months ago. Yeah, I thought you were black, but you just talk like you're gonna talk to me talking
He was one of the folks. Yeah
You sound like yeah. Yeah, I'm not black being serious, but but then I heard Goddy. I was like, I was like, oh shit
We're going on my team you put on psyche on my team
It can make a hundred dollars a day. No, what's going on? So I can what you gotta go got it
What y'all got going on? No, we're just chillin man. No, yeah
Nothing major tonight. I'm gonna figure out just chill
No wars breaking out
Yeah, yeah, yeah summer handled Canada so everything's cool
You know, you know, I've been doing psychic readings, man. You know, I had a problem with doing
You did readings what kind of readings?
You know, I tried 350 dollars. I I charge 200. I charge almost a hundred dollars an hour. Oh, now it's a hundred
I can promise you that
Yeah, most of my readings for like corporate people and stuff like that.
I shouldn't say this, but most of my shit is for corporate people.
It looks like you're out Canada.
If you know what I mean.
Hey, can you do a quick reading right now?
You understand? You understand that guy?
Yeah, I understand. Can you do one real quick right now?
For who?
Take your pick, anybody.
Yeah, for who?
I'm saying take your pick.
The one for psych he needs one. I mean, I don't know I mean like I think
This is advertising like you don't have to charge you put a car down for sight. Hey, let's see what's like
I do a free for sake me. I'll pull a card out the side. Yeah, it doesn't have to be crazy long just
You will see to government. Well, I'm a governmental site. Oh shit, but Godie. I'm a governmental site
Is this the one that you like you leave your body astral planning and shit like that?
Yeah, yeah, that's like he's gonna float above you while you're sleeping. Well, we don't that's
Astral ray gun
I already got caught I got a card already for on psyche like you know a car to pull for you saying
The page of pinnacles cycle. I got the page of pinnacles for psyche. That's good. So money's gonna grow
You know what that means, honey?
Yeah, it's just like a seed that you know why I can psyche the pages pinnacles because you trying to find yourself
Yeah, you're trying to find yourself into this tarot card region and stuff like you're trying to find yourself
I how can you use the cars and help other people?
But it's kind of like you kind of confuse about the cars because you you you buy so many different decks and stuff
Go ahead
I've actually had
as a tarot card reader, I did
paid readings
in a 2020
during the whole lockdown
show a governmental
psyche
on the governmental level
but I do know how
best to
I got another car
go ahead
Mean argue good. I got another car for you. I'm psyche. I got another car for you
Go ahead. I got the world upside down. Okay, so something's not coming to an end, right? You know what that means the world upside down, right?
Well, yeah, it means like I'll be stuck in a cycle or something. Well, no, it's come it's like it's like you're you're too
No, it's kind of it's good. No, no, no, don't it's like it's kind of like you're in between
Like what you want to do is like you do want to do this and you want to do this and you want to do that
It's like you're kind of not focus on one thing
But you have the world in your hands, but reverse is showing that that's your you're you're not
We're making very judgmental interpretation. I mean, I'm sorry. I don't mean
Showing you kind of like you the ways that you want to do it, but you don't want to do it is
Okay, well go ahead saying what you said i'm not saying i'm not saying you're wrong with like the cards right because like the cards make
Are making sense, but it's like you're no i'm just saying that the car the car negative spin on it like oh yeah because the world
Yeah, you know what the world car means it's kind of like
Right world is like you know coming through a cycle. It's kind of like it's kind of like for you
It's kind of like what cars should i do like you like you bought so many?
I don't have a question about cards. I mean, I've been basically I just have like I have like 50 decks, right?
But I it's kind of like the cars
Right. You heard that I had 50 decks, right? You heard about that. I'm sorry. I don't want to argue with you
But I'm just saying you're interpreting
No, it's kind of like you kind of you're not you're kind of
Well, go ahead. Can you do a reading on me, sir?
Thank you. You're kind of so much into it psyching that you use so many different cards like you're not
I don't use so many to do it on you. Yeah, I don't do government readings, but
Well, thank you for thank you for reading though. I'd like to I'd like the card
So I got with a page of pinnacles in the what's your name summer. Yeah, I got you. Yeah, it's summer. That's my real name
Well, I couldn't get into because psyche is kind of like your it's psyche psyche is coming
I'm argumentative, but it's like it's kind of like you you want so many different kind of cars like you buy cars
But you're not really getting in tune to the cars
So you need to stay focused on one deck instead of trying to get so many different day
I'm very focused on the writer way. You need to stay focused on one day first
Most of them are like, you know, just basically the writer, but it's like their own version
Yeah, you you're on the right track, but he's kind of like you confused with so many deck that you got
Thank you. Thank you
Well, let's do summer. Well, what is summer?
Who was summer?
I'm right here. Oh
Got summer right here the magician
reverse
Summers that you you're trying to find that way of trying to find that enlightenment stage
But it's like you want to be part of the like the car readers and stuff
But you haven't got to that stage of doing it yet of being a car reader
So you want to be a man?
Everything about this is but you haven't took the techniques of being a
Is the card I think I want to be you what you think I want to be a card reader
That too and at the same time is like you kind of
Now I think you're kind of like kind of met and drunk too, but um, but um
The problem that I see with you arms like you it's like you've been drinking a lot because you have like the problems that you have
You've been drinking
He doesn't drink
I don't drink at all.
No alcohol.
I remember you read for us and then it's like,
you would say like we're drunks
and like all this kind of stuff.
And it's like, I remember now and it's like,
I was like, maybe that's why you ever come back.
But that means one of your family members didn't drink.
Why would you get a card about who the answer is?
It's one of your family members that drank.
No, no one in my family actually drinks.
It's one of your family members that drank a lot.
No, no, my family doesn't drink.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
You can't tell me what my, we don't drink.
Nobody nobody in my family drinks
My father doesn't drink my mother's dead. My husband doesn't drink my children don't drink
Yeah
I mean, have I ever drank sure I've drank long time ago. That's that's what he meant
I don't drink so I smoke weed
But I drink no alcohol and I don't do any drugs so
And by the way, I don't want to be a card reader either so
Oh, okay. What's it's like? Um, it's like
I would be honest, I don't need no cars to do this shit
What else are you so far you're I could tell by you on summer is that like you have a lot of problems about what's going on
in your life and your family's like
No, I don't mean
It's like you've been holding back a lot of times about what you got to say about your family
Something something about how you you don't like one part of your family like is a problem with your family or stuff that you don't like
I think your cards are off big time. Not one thing you said about the man
I've been married for almost 20. I've been almost ma'am at 30 years ago. I've been married for 20 years
What are you talking about? I've been married for 18 years actually
I've been married for
Everyone have a good day, I hope
Yeah, one second
I'm not satisfied in my marriage so I drink but I don't drink I want to be a
card reader but I don't want to be a card reader and now I'm not satisfied in my
marriage that I've been married to for 18 years. Oh shit, here we go. I think you're
way off.
Another one, but no the thing that that is it's by it's by your voice
I could see the tour I could see the turmoil in your boy
So they're holding even women
Brothers
Man let's talk
I can't
Truth Apollo or Goddy or psyche. Have you all ever seen me drink?
I see you smoke
You might drink you might drink a wine cool day now, and then I don't know that I'm just playing
I see you smoking that drink drink water
Man so many you would different type you would different type on you
Stop interrupting you're being rude miss at your bitch ass. I'm ain't talking to you for
Ever seen summer smoke weed
Agree nothing's right now, and he even said I don't drink. I know I do not drink
And so you remind me of me you like a shark in the water you don't know paneling is a
You have problems in your family right now that I see.
You have a lot of problems though in your family summer, don't you?
No, I don't.
Don't you have problems in your family though summer?
What about your brother's summer?
Not, sir.
My brother is dead and has been dead for over a decade.
Jesus Christ.
We'll always go to private.
These people always get to touch it.
Shut your bitches up.
Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang Bang
Every time you make a fool out of yourself every time you open your mouth
Every time you talk you make a foreign a teller
You don't even want to hit my panel no mo you come in my check
You know what I'm gonna do to you Apollo you're gonna call me out
I'ma troll your bitch
This nigga bro this
Bro, he used to come out. He's to come to my panel right up. Hello. I got a lot of niggas over there
It's a whole lot of niggas over there. They got to
Even back
Don't
They turned them out
They barricued his ass
You're trolling me the only one you make fun of is yourself
I
He's very limited in his work up man
You grab a musty ass cat that smell like ass
This new York I saw were really really strange
All of them I seriously
Michael knows
Bro, what the fuck are you talking about? I got a smaller challenge. That's why you're here to get the shoes, right?
No, hold on. Hold on. These niggas is retarded
You don't get no views shoes on
I get I probably get just as many I probably get just as many views as some of them get over there on talk you ish
Uh-huh probably more
Are you jealous through son?
Are you jealous to turn?
Are you jealous?
Shut the fuck up. You're totally going to fly in your mouth.
Shut your bitch yourself.
You're totally going to fly in your mouth.
Shut your mouth.
Yeah, you sound like this doors, you know, you you wind them up in the dog and dog
And you sound like AI motherfucker, you sound like you ain't even real
Robot motherfucker
This nigga hooked on fine X man hooked on telephonic do not talk it mother fucker
You need a whole translator why you want a panel with you?
I don't understand shit you saying
I'm trying to teach you Leroy wax on wax off. You're not talking motherfucker. I
Have a question. Are you trolling me now?
No, I ain't trolling you now. I'm trying to teach you motherfucker. I got the whip I got the whip in my hand
I'm gonna beat you into submission
I want to know, I want to know to be a gangster like you.
Apollo, you know I rock with you, man.
You know, I got to give you a heart.
I want to learn to be a gangster,
a harker gangster like you.
I want to learn to be John Gatchin,
to have a mafia film.
Oh, good luck, man.
But it's just like my chef buddy.
Man, I got niggas in the chat
Bro, let me know what I'm saying to you is working. I got niggas in the chat laughing at your ass niggas. I told you bro
Yes, you kind of my channel, bro
Niggas me niggas keep talking when my channel is dead, bro
I get nigga come on I get like five six hundred views when I go live bro 700 views 800 views when I go live
I ain't tripping about y'all hating ass niggas
I bet if you're unentertaining ass went live right now nobody will pull up to watch that shit you niggas y'all niggas is boring
Y'all ain't funny. No one ain't no money. No one ain't pulling up to watch our bullshit
You niggas is trash y'all garbage throw yourself away in your channel where you trash me
I bet you started the channel right now. Nobody would pull up to that motherfucker not even sight nigger. You piece of shit shut the fuck up
Can you make it as soon as without saying but
Sight man, what are you talking about? I'm saying
You need to pay attention
You can't make a sentence
I would just use one example
Man, don't worry about how I talk about it
You be broke
Shut your ass up nigga
You a fucking alien
You can burly
Express yourself
They're gonna deport you to the car world.
You're gonna get deported to the Grand Canyon, Motherfucker.
So don't do it, Motherfucker.
Don't do it, son.
Don't respect my case.
You need to put your ass in the traffic.
You need to be trafficked back to where you came from, Motherfucker.
So don't do it, son.
Don't respect my case.
Put your ass in the back of a U-Haul and traffic your ass back to wherever you came from,
like, damaged like a damaged can do it.
Get your get your ass the fuck I get you when you're broken English the fuck out of here
What the me I can say fuck out of here with your broken English man
My you're fucking my meat tomorrow not surrender
Be proud be American through some
Fuck with me man. Yeah, I'll cook any of these niggas over here. Man. Nobody can fuck with me man
Anybody niggas anybody niggas that includes you too nigga
You say what
Yeah, yeah, it's who the fuck phone in LA site man. Why I got us why they come up here all every day talking at you
I can't use any word
Is it guess what my bad brain or you might
I'm gonna say
Uh
You're gonna cook me truth knob a prairie mr. Uh, what page babe, I wouldn't cook you, you know, I got
Man that nigga that nigga driving that nigga driving in the mother
My negro driving under
The failure at Characters, that's who he is
Look at easy, look at easy in the chat down there saying that if your convo was way better before, look at easy
Look at his old chihuahua looking at it. You know, he got to say something every time. This is a good chat
You sound like Apollo man
Apollo that's how you sound when you talk you sound just like this nigga
I
Wasn't him man. It was a
follow like
Oh
the other dude
with the triangle Michael or whatever
I
was trying to get
the uh, yeah, I guess his terror cars didn't tell him his life sucks me
I'll be hating in the chat. He said the truth don't want to bring anything to the panel or is he just here for attention?
man
Get the fuck on i'm gonna be in my business niggas be a pretty yelling arguing i come up here trying to throw jokes y'all
The conversation was we good for shut your bitch ass up remind your business
Easy you like michael jackson dirty dying
Get a motherfucking ponytail i cut that shit off shut the fuck up
No threats
No, I'm playing man. I ain't gonna threaten the guy. I'm just I'll play don't take me serious man. It's all good, man
It's cool. I got it
Like now we're Apollo go man Apollo get your ass bro. Oh, why you scared hit my panels now, bro
Why don't hit my leak no more man? The Negroes. Did you dirty over there bro? Now you don't hit my panel no more man
It's all good. I tell me you're alone next time you come back. I'm like, you know, you know what y'all leave me alone
Man, he's sensitive man. Leave me alone. Is that is that what you want, bro? I'll do it my turn
Hey, man, I'll back up off. I'm leaving alone man
Hey, Gotti, I heard there's a rapture Wednesday
Yeah, that's what somebody told me. There was like summer the rapture. It's actually Wednesday. I was like, oh, okay
You say there's a rapture someone, you know who do you know what the wrap
I'm gonna throw a bunch of clothes all over the neighborhood and I'm gonna go scream and they left us behind
They left us behind
The rap the rap's you gonna be ice
It's gonna be ice. It's gonna be a ice you will for taking more focus like pop all the back the way it came from
So the tomorrow at the next week, we ain't gonna hear Paula no more because the ice rapture doesn't happen
They don't took him back beyond the ice wall wherever he came from
Beyond that down here dinosaur motherfucker. He just
Well, Paula go to
Before he was triangle head was sucking your nuts basically and now he's all like look out for gaudi because he's not on panel
Because his mic's broke and he can't be tarot guards
No, he means look out for me. He means y'all need to look out for me. Somebody said why is everybody mean to choose?
Oh, let me tell you why they don't like me over here, uh, which Mary is I come over here and barbecue their ass
They don't like it. They not used to that day. They ain't they ain't used to a man coming back coming over here
Just cooking their ass and laughing in their face. That's why that's why easy don't like me because I'll barbecue his old
Dyke looking ass. He's like, he's like, he's like, he got 10 degree. He'll be a baby mama
You like a single baby mama easy cameras. That's why you got beat under the mode of I wasn't anything a beach one of the car
Look you changing the oil. Shut your ass up. You don't like me sneak over here
You like you weird over here, that's why they don't like me miss wish marries. I come over and get a ass the blues
I don't give fuck who it is
Anybody mean the truth zone
Like y'all got
Follows in the back. You see everybody like you say buddy. You see everybody in the chat laughing at you easy
Yeah, he was like bro. Look you trying to train drop trains the fucking transmission after he got done with you, nigga
You beat your ass under the street
You was under you down there with the rats in the Ninja Turtles when they got done with your ass, man
You try to drop the motor what?
Money, what up money? What up, man?
Goddamn tell me is me
Hello
Yeah
Whatever your fucking name is in the chat next time I go live. I want you to pull up and hit my link
I bet every dollar in my I bet you a hundred dollars right now. You won't pull up in my link time
I bet you won't I know you won't you gonna talk shit in that chat down there. You ain't gonna hit this link
You won't hit my I know you won't I'm back. I can guarantee you won't cuz you're gonna get cooked
How are we done cooking?
Are we done cooking? Yeah, I'm done. Yeah, I got it man turkey done
Yeah, so how we go
What's that? Thank you your bike's kind of love it. I'm but who's who's Mike is going
Right there, who's that I think it's Bill Michaels Michael
Michael your mic is like I'm a god. He may ask you a question. Got it, bro. What up, man?
This nigga, this Negro, this uh, this dyke, this Jamaican dyke in the chat with him, people like, people like, Carlos San Diego
Maria, Maria, remind me of a East Side Story
Easy spell he got whooped in Spanish Harlem
He livin' life just like a movie star
Easy, not easy, got it
Bro has anybody made you laugh tonight on this motherfucking
You hear me got it has any has anybody made you laugh tonight on this fan
Maybe he's laughing about you man, I'm asking him a question God has any of these niggas made you laugh as easy made you laugh
These niggas these niggas be up in front of these these niggas be up here crying
All right, then these niggas ain't funny man, these niggas be up here crying complaining
Okay, that's not in the tree last night. I can't get shut the fuck up
That's your barn
Oh, man, I went to his house and I pulled up and you know, I was about to fight him. No, I don't read lame
But you almost died last night. Who cares you should have died
I'm gonna trash back and throw yourself away
Sike Mark wants a reading. Okay, Mark. I got you
On the really on the rapture. Okay. Well, let's go if you killed it man. You fucking killed it
If I get a donation, I'll do a bit more on the rapture from somebody how much you want
The meanest like for the let me see between five and ten. Hey, Michael hit him up ten bucks
But I think that's a no though
Um, yeah, um, cause it's like that's, but it's, cause I think I did one the other night to go to and it's like, it was like, you know, I didn't want for the world and stuff like that.
And it was an interesting reading though, it's like, uh, you know, cause it was like, I think the 10 of cups was in the past.
So I think like a lot of our happy, hot, happiest things have like, you know, your past, but I like to think that more happiness is to come.
What do you think Gaudi?
You can't talk dude, I'm done
Truth or killed it, man. He fucking killed
Which Mary was asking in the chat for your channel
If you've got a wrench she got a wrench
It's tight just typing truths on productions man, you know, I host panels just like site
Yeah
I'm not like site, but I you know, I'll talk about different shit, you know
A lot of these haters a lot of these haters be saying our truth zone channel was born. No, no, it's entertaining
It's all entertainment. We make people laugh. We make
Yeah, you just mad the jokes are lame now. They're not they're not lame. You just mad cuz your ass
Prepare to hear the n-words a million times
Man, I fuck with smash man because I cooked his ass on one of these panels over here
But he came over to my panel in the chat. He said what's up truths on I gave him a little wrench
I said, you know, I respect that but I like that bro. You know, that's what black people do. We joke man
We tell jokes we laugh with each other. Yeah, I think it's be tight asses, man
Who your corduroy's down, man? You weren't your pants past your belly button
I
You know, he's not black, right
Oh boy, you just talk about the smash
Yeah, no, no, I'm saying yeah, I know that he cool though. He cool
Yeah
He's solid
Well, I don't really mind being joked on, but, you know, I've already, you know, I, I, I, I, I, I, I conquered, uh, Fringe the Source and, and Shannon, so I can, can't, can't, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can, can
You know, that sucks, but um
Trick like is gone. Um, twip kick is I don't know. I think trip kick might still be up, but a twip kick is brown
And uh, but then I checked on the rumble and he is posting like, you know on his rumble page still
And uh, there was a new one of me on there too
It's kind of a shorter one
But uh, it was you know, just the same stuff that's going on
But he does document a lot of like, you know
Times I'm being talked about what I'm not even in the room. It's kind of crazy and
You know, but it's certain person
He's like, you know, it was kind of sad like I did I put her song to music, you know
I can it's a very it's a shorter song
Here's his song. She she wrote me a poem and then I put it to music. I put it to so here's the poem
I have who you talking about
Okay, so being opposed to this poem and then I was on our show and she's like what she's like
I posted this poem and it was about you. No, it was like a message to me and stuff and so
Here's here does I put it to music?
Wishing you happiness
Leave in mind behind
In the silence
I'll hold on to the past
And cherish it
I'll love you every day
My love
Yeah, am I supposed to respond to that?
I mean, it's very nice.
You know, it's one of those things like,
oh, I love you, but I can't be standing around you.
She's telling me.
That's the way of reaching out to you.
She's not even around me though.
It's like, and we already are far apart.
It's like, I don't understand.
She's here in spirit.
No, she's not.
And it's the person I met kind of,
but I keep trying to see if that person's there.
Smoke him if you got him, I'm rolling a blunt.
Not drinking, I'm rolling a blunt.
Yeah, I mean, I have to say, Michael,
it's like sometimes men as terror readers,
I'm not trying to criticize you or anything,
but it's like Chris K is a similar thing.
It's like,
It's like this heavy projection
Like above of like the interpretation or and it's like, okay. Well, and then it's like, okay
No, that's not true. And then it's like bubbling down on it and stuff like that. And it's like, yes, it is important to like say
Things with confidence
But it's like, you know, for me, I can tell when you were reading, I think it happened last time too, you were telling people, oh, your husband is this and this, and then they feel like, no, we're happily married, and you're like, no, you're saying all this, just like you're assisting.
And kind of like, more to what the, if you are doing it for $200 an hour, that's quite an outrageous fee as well, you better be worth it.
But it's like.
He is upskill fine
Maybe he's not trying to find things something wrong may think it but I think no sometimes men are just really one-track mind about like
Psycho-psychologist that I guarantee you if you start charging a thousand dollars a reading you'll get it
Well, you know, it's like I just would not feel I mean if I was like, you know, you got to know listen
You got to be serious about it and just do it. I am serious about it
And it's like and I but it's like I feel like I would like to be accessible not to just like, you know
Millionaires and things like that, right? It's like I want I think to be I'm not saying just do that
I'm just saying if you wanted to charge a thousand dollars somebody will be out there to pay you that
I can certainly put together a small reading, you know, it's like it would be you know, but it would be like, you know
A lot of a lot of stuff. It would be like, you know, oh, yeah, it has to be deep
I would do I would like basically do it like you know, do like hours with somebody, you know, and
Get go top to bottom, but um, thank you
Hey, um, I'm looking forward like I think Tracy wants me to do one of the astrology reports for her like where I'd you know
We'll incorporate some like art and music into it too with it with like the symbol is a lot of the symbols of the chart
and like that's such a good way to like
Connect with your chart and especially the head and I would say that's a good way to learn anything is like, you know type
You know type the information you need to learn put it into a song
Then like just play the song over and over because songs are catchy and the memorable and you'll
Probably pick some
Information up faster than you normally would so that's a kind of good strategy if you're trying to learn something exactly so
What do you guys think? I think that's it
I think it's a good idea your chart and things like that. Yeah. Yeah, you do charts like that. You get much of the narrow
Well, I'm working on it
But I think it's so so new that it's like I need to just package it the right way present it the right way to the right audience
right and it's like then yes, but it's like
Like a lot of my audience here is
Through basically panel panel bursting and so not everybody is like quite
Into the spirit spirituality the same way I am or to the depth I
But I do and glad a lot of people are willing to learn and stuff like that or wanting to learn and
So you said you said I would you saw me on the tan man show, right?
I didn't see you. Somebody told me that you were there. Oh, well, you know how he operates his panel
He has people call in like literally call in
Yeah, oh, yeah
Maybe you should yeah, maybe you should do a burner phone thing with readings and have people pay you like that call the burner phone number
If you want to get like a legit reading for like, you know
I can set up a you know a text now number that they could call in during the show
Yes, like because it doesn't really happen up here when you have a panel up here on stream yard
Yeah, and you do readings up here you do it for us, which is great
You know you do the free readings, but to do that like the high-paying readings
That has to be one-on-one stuff
Yeah, and I mean I am on the panel it is a much discounted rate to like a private one-on-one
Yeah, because you got Apollo up here fucking mumbling through somebody else's reading nobody wants to hear that
Nobody wants to hear that
He's back there meditating
That's what he's back there doing. Paul, where you going, paolo? Why you meet your mic?
And I say keep your mic and you the matter of fact you got it
Easy in the chat talking about it got born. I left and came back. You ain't never go nowhere, man
You're so fucking man. You're so aligned. Well, he went to change the oil
Yeah, man. He's still he's in a coma for for months after that beating he took
He's after the fight you like who jumped me. No, you ain't get jumped bro
Yeah, you got hands and feet put on you by one man
He's like, man, I got jacuzza squad got jumped by 20 people. No, nigga
You got he thought he got beat up by invite PD. He doesn't know bro
You need the police ain't be chill with them billy pads. You guys stomped out by one person, but
That nigga turned the two mo fucking octopus he had eight hands
You should have bit the bullet like me Roy
You should have bit you should have bit the bullet like me Roy in the last dragon
He catches bullets with a stop talking but did
He bit the bullet like Leroy
Who's Leroy?
The one with the last dragon, he do call the bullet with his two
Leroy Jenkins
Hey, uh, it's all good easy, bro. You're good, bro.
Oh, no one takes you serious, man.
You can't do that up here. You know, they don't.
No one takes you serious.
I can't do what it's for sure.
You can't be hurting feelings like that.
They just joke, bro.
That's why these niggas are sensitive over here, bro.
I don't think that's why people can do what I do.
I know they can cry about it.
They choose all the joke, you know.
Shut your bitches.
Shut your over the system, man.
This is Psyche Tarot.
They're not some hardcore motherfuckers.
They're going to be able to be roasted like that.
They all going to cry, man.
Yeah, they be crying too much over here, bro. I'll be having a lease on time like Brian. I heard his shit man
Here they go crying again. Damn. They come over in joke. They're getting
Made easy leave you see you made easy crying leave now easy be I man
He's I've been joking easy though, man. He give me easy good, bro. He's just ready said peace outside. What happened to your rules?
My rule is like, you know
I mean, it's like he's like this guy is kind of just like loud
He's not being serious, he's just joking around
Like I don't be like a strict teacher I like expect adults to like be able to like
I hate
I'm sorry. He's I'm not not easy. It's like mind me to disrespect you
I'm saying like, you know
That's the thing. It's like I like people so like
You know you with not easy not easy
Was you worried about the rules when you took a five-hour Greyhound bus ride all the way to another burrow in New York when you
When they put it batteries in your back to fight Alexander
When they gave you fifty cents a cigarette, you were dumb.
You took a five-hour bus ride for a quarter and a cigarette. What's wrong with you? You got to be slow
You came out of you came out your mama's pussy feet first me that dropped on your head. They beat you with the dummy or the retarded stick
You extra slow
Did the rules apply when you went when you pulled up there was his name
Krip trying to fight with him when you put out a cracker jack knife a butter knife, huh?
Do the rules apply then suck it's your fault buddy. You put the coin in him
Do the rules apply then when you be bought when you be doxxing people sucker
Did they apply then now you won't be crying about rules sucker as you getting your ass cooked
You look like a she look like a shaved puppy you look like a baby rock ball with no teeth. That's your
Venezuelan I don't know what you
Just let your soul glow as you easy spraying that jerk that overreactive in your head Nick shut up Nick
It's too funny. It's a sorry trim zone. You have to Lee. I ain't gonna I'm gonna stay here right here
Just to get on your nerves. I'm gonna stay here for the rest of the night
What you gonna do about you don't know you don't
You have no choice of power
I got a deep bag of insoles. I got a deep bag of jokes for your sucker as easy. I don't care about you
You guys don't even gotta follow the rules. Oh, you gonna go cry. We're gonna cry about it tomorrow, too
Go live and cry about it. Then something so me so we put sue me on sue me on judge Judy, man. Sue me
That's your fault
To me
I'll stop when you learn how to talk proper English fluently
But I'll say
You go first in English yourself. I would hate to I would hate to call Papa John's and have a motherfucker like you or answer the phone
But they will have to make take your out there and turn this extra cheese, but no kid
Get somebody else's phone my nigga. I'm not
a
Magic going to a chicken shagging. I'm taking your order. You want extra crispy, but they would you take a name?
But a covert mass
Hey, hey, hey, I was like put that wish Mary's a chat on the screen
The truth zone is funny though. You said nice. What I'm talking about. This is why they don't like me over here
I'm over here in barbecue. They asked man. They get to try and about it
I'm not gonna get mad. I'm not gonna get let you up a barbecue your way. We can't hear you
Imagine going to church and hearing a pastor like Apollo
I'm saying the gender gender chapter fly buddy. I'm gonna talk about how Jesus
No, I'm about to cry don't do it man
He's just joking with you
I take it serious
Michael nobody can hear you man your phone's breaking up they got your phone tapped
Man just coming up truth now you got something to talk about
Now I know man. I know everybody over here man. God. I've been coming around here for a long time. I know summer
Know I know Amanda. I know Christine. I know Bronzberg. I know
My panel morning anybody from over here shout the eggs. I want
Some used to come to my panel. I know all these people over here, bro
I know everybody over here. I don't even know you got a stream
Yeah, I know everybody over here, bro. Yeah, I've been knowing them
In the one that's how you get over to this community because he was the answer summit
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Community support community so now we all support each other
For sure for sure. Yeah, I come from a different sector than them
But I just you know, like you said sectors coming together me and someone I had I run in some of you don't just like me though
She's like a shark in water
She gets you yellow and she'll yell for two hours straight. Like, you know what let me go ahead and be my mic I
Try they got a try doing a yellow match for some four hours straight. It was a tie
Yeah, it's no point man. Everybody's doing the same shit. You're yelling for hours and hours. What's the point? Yeah?
I did that was something we did that last night, you know what?
Yeah, so you know what you can't win the screaming match with this lady here
You're gonna have to show jokes. I'm just relentless. She won't stop. No, she won't stop. That's why you know, that's what I like about
Should be on her last leg just yelling at you to
Related some and through so are you related? No, we're from the same city though
Oh
Okay, make sense. Are we related to Apollo?
Summer bring the suit with you on some outreach give people something to laugh about
This is just the internet personality man, it's all I just know you won't do it you won't do it in person
Not a joke to real life. I've always been like is I've always had a
Was I was little man. I've always told jokes man even in school
I'm gonna talk a school named valley high school niggas will come give me a came and come roasted to do it real quick
I'll go roast a man. You never just stand up. No, man. Yeah, you gotta try it at least once man. It's good shit
No, this is my type of comedy. I love shit like this like
In the sector and the sector I come from they be over there joking on a whole lot man
You got dudes over there funnier than me
The next I want to
Get boring seriously. You said what yeah, we bet you what y'all talking about though. I'm good
You say I get born who wants to hear you talk for two hours straight motherfucking?
You talk the same shit over and over
Don't listen to Apollo talk for three hours straight Paul you talked the same shit over and over
So are you you a TPP reject man?
Hating on all women
You never heard my shit. No
You repeat the same hateful speech and make fun about all women like what?
Like Amanda it's like you got somebody in the back, bro. What I say about Amanda
I don't want to repeat it
Now go ahead repeat it
Say it
You're a fucking liar then
Do you know the funny thing is Apollo could hang anywhere he wanted to but he loves our community
So he's not he's just like us
Whether he realizes no the difference is some a lot of it's some a lot of it was there. I don't start shit
I use it. Oh, both
People now
I summon what makes him
You hear me Russian what what makes him just like you will if he but he's in the now
What makes him just like you?
Because if he wasn't if he wasn't with the drop one he starts all kind of shit
He day he's he does a lot of slab weight little comments or whatever
But the fact is if he wasn't like us we're all alike to an extent because none of us would be here if we weren't
So there's that and he's faithfully been in these communities
He follows us how that same reason Apollo got here
So, you know what I mean? He's like I said, you know
He tried to portray shit differently, but he likes it. He loves this shit. Where's he time? No, I know I know
He's intrigued by the American culture
because
You have to be American. Yeah, he loves it, you know, he does because every time I go live
He pops up in the chair. He's come up on my panel, but they they cook
I'll be honest with you
I think Apollo and subsets almost does because from what I could pick up from Apollo
Without going into much Apollo does some good work
But he does some heavy work from time to time and sometimes when you do really heavy work
And this is I mean this is why I hang out here is because you need to fuck a release
You need to be able to have fun. You need to be able to talk a little shit
You know, I mean it just takes you out of what you the the the gloom and the depressing
I don't go or I don't cross lines. I don't go under the ball.
Oh, yeah, Paula. Cut the bull.
Man, here's a board of crap, baby.
Should he be a man?
You can cross a lot because you're hanging in this community.
Everybody's unstable that hangs out in this community.
Maybe, but again, I don't talk about families
like this triangle idiot before with your family.
Man, here we go. Here he goes.
This is a triangle.
Hey, Sike, you got somebody in the back, man.
Wake your ass up, man. Yes, like Amanda wants to come up and take care of her out of you. I have more, I have more
self-control. I gotta tell people all the time, if you just, my, my thing is like, even with me, right, people know I'm
gonna go to hell, right? If you don't think, figure that out by now, then I don't know what to tell people. So my
thing is, if you decide to get an argument with me, if you decide to go around, around with me, don't clutch your fucking
pearls when I decide to talk about whatever the fuck I want to talk about.
I don't care you can talk whatever you want, but anyone be a yes man, that's the problem
right?
I don't have any other people around me, you know how many people fuck it, I get on their
nerves when they talk shit about me on a daily basis, so where's the yes people at?
Come on now, come on now, you only want to have a yes man and boot lick us around.
Well you're wrong.
You're wrong. I'm even I'm even married to somebody that their political views are different the man so apollo
I'm sorry, but that's just your opinion, but it's
Would be around me none of you would be around me if I had yes people around me. Are you fucking kidding?
Let me tell you something real quick. Let me tell you something
How many arguments we don't got into because we don't had disagreements a billion
So
I'm not no yes, man. It's summer. We don't get into a plethora of fucking arguments
Amanda's a man though Amanda's a man
That we're all but that's what makes all of us. We are all very strong. Thank you. I was born a female
We're all very strong and very opinionated people
So for you to sit there and act like especially the people that's on this panel right now
So for you apollo to be like, oh subver you have yes been around you apollo. I'm sorry
But I I have to definitely disagree with you on that because nobody on this panel can kiss them
Tristan, I was just in the shower and I was trying to shame, shame, I was trying to shave my legs.
And then I hear, let your soul...
Oh, you like that. Don't you baby? It was funny. What you like that? Don't you baby? I almost fell in the damn shower
I'm funny when you like that. I thought I better put this razor up. This is dangerous
I'm sorry. It was fucking hilarious and anybody that is our age knows exactly where that fucking shit came from
Apollo you may not know but you need to go and rent a movie called coming to America. You it's an old movie
And I will hook you up with a link. Maybe if I can find it, you got to watch it, brother
You need subtitles. No, I can find it. I can find it. Yes
It's an old movie from the 80s. It's got Eddie Murphy in it in our senior hall and
It's about a guy who always was playing
Prince right? Yes, Africa print. Yeah, I saw it
It is I mean that's just like one of the best movies of our time. I think you know
Man, you want to have a man. You want to have a good laugh? You ain't got a word about the kind you ain't gonna
We're about to host all in your business
Come the truth zone come the death row there we go
Yeah, you don't want to hold you don't want to host all in your business muting you I do mutinix
But you don't you don't want to host all in your business being boring
Come to true zone.
I'm just me take me leave me. I don't give a damn, you know, but in apollo's defense
He is kind of jaded about americans and i'm gonna say this and I don't want it to open the kennel worms
He was in the Middle East as an interpreter at one time and so he's been around
American military and so
Thank you, Amanda. He has seen us at our very worst. Now. I guess you ask Apollo now. She just talks. No
I'm not doxing him at all fucking ass motherfucker now listen. Nobody knows about Apollo. Okay, I know now
And now I know exactly what anyway. Oh, he's not an interpreter anymore. He works for the UN
No, he doesn't anyway
He's seen some horrible shit that we've done in the Middle East. I mean, you can't blame me. Oh
That's what you like like you like it hot, huh?
And that's a point Amanda you all these people making the you know talking about something they don't have a zero clue
What they're talking about?
they've never been there all they've seen is pictures and you know hey you know
we sit in the coaches sitting in the coaches with the fat asses you know
we're watching some stupid news you know what the fuck you talking about
Um, I don't know anything by watching the news
What the fuck do you know summer come back?
Um, I wanted to tell you something before you left. What do I know? I've been in Kuwait in
I asked I asked him what he knows. I didn't ask you. Okay. I'll just want to be clear
Oh, oh kidneys
They won't some of your
You get somebody backstage sight man. Okay? Oh, you're not the only one in the world with world experience
Fucking acts like you know, I know I know that you have it cause he trust me
I didn't say me. I read between the lines. I
Were hiding between the light moves. I know don't make assumptions
I didn't you did and all I was gonna say to Apollo why yes, I can understand and Amanda
I do get what you're saying
I mean we have most of us haven't seen the things in the Middle East
But at the same time I can look at him and say that you know
There's some shit that happens here in America and some of us have had some you know crazy shit
So that's why I said I believe that's why Apollo hangs out in these kind of communities because the same reason I do dude
But when you see heavy shit and you see
Insane shit on it, you know, whatever when you're doing what you're doing you got to have some kind of release
So even though Apollo has he says I don't cross those standards and that's great
That's great for him, but some of us, you know, I'm saying it is what it is when you know, it is what it is
But we're all
We're all a little unstable or we wouldn't be hanging in these communities
Okay, I have a PTSD rating for it. I'm not fucking ashamed of it. I earned that shit man. It's awesome
But what are you gonna say I put it in the chat earlier and you might have stepped away
But scotis toad Giselle Maxwell to pretty much fuck off today. Yeah. Yep. Yeah
I posted I've been to post it on YouTube, but I did post it on my other socials
But yeah, the Supreme Court said they will not be here in her case. She could take her ass back to her as a
I haven't read the decision yet. I can't wait, but when I heard it come across my or saw it come across my phone
I was like there you go, bitch. That's what you fucking when you dumb cut
When you get it when you read it. Will you send it to me?
Yeah, I can do that. I can download it and send it to him
Like that bitch fuck that bitch, but you know what he didn't get asked Trump for a pardon. Did you see that? Oh?
Yes, and it's my understanding like I know 50 cent
Already went to the White House and told Trump
Behind the doors not to give it to him, and I think some other people have told him the same thing
So he better not fucking pardon that little piece of garbage. I don't I don't I'll be honest with you
I really don't think Trump's gonna pardon him. I just don't and not even because of what his charges are
It's more for I just don't think he's going to
A lot of other fucked up. He did he he did. He wants trump to party. That's crazy. That's fucked that
Well, he's not gonna have a chance for that and so like Trump. Yeah, I forget that
Well, no, Trump could do it tomorrow with a swagger
Yeah, he's not going
He's not he's it's not good for his social social, you know what I mean?
I know some people are saying well some people said that they may he might try to do it to try to you know
Bring more voters, but that's not the black dude to you. Sorry
He's a piece of shit and he's not gonna get you any votes because nobody wants to sorry us right now
No, fuck that fool. I mean, there's a handful of weirdos that thinks he's okay still, but those are fucking probably predator shoot
So he got he got off easy with four with how many months did he get how many years he gets?
Should I say?
He got four years
But I mean, of course he got off because of the powerful people he has around him, right?
But as we all know and anybody that knows anything and truth, you know a little bit about the music
Is shit. I mean this motherfucker's been doing shit for years. So just because today it wasn't a
In a court of law we all know he's a fucking he's a predator
He was involved in Biggie's dad and in two pox so he can go
Well, and he was involved
He was involved. He just got sentenced and a man acts he was being charged with Rico and trafficking
But they got away with it. They proved it in court. I'm telling you right now
They proved it but they are not they weren't gonna do it because he had powerful people around him letting him off
Just like Epstein when Epstein got charged the first couple times all those cases
Fucker went away too, and then he got a sweetheart deal on something
He should have never got a sweetheart deal on so when you were in these positions
What powerful people around you they get away with shit and they had it what I feel like happened
He did he was fill in his nuts and he thought he was too big
He got into it with the liquor people and then boom next thing you know the motherfucker said oh you want to be smart
You want to run your mouth boom and then they sat his ass down
They sat him down for four years with the man act and they didn't give him the Rico and shit
But I mean, you know the next thing he'll end up DEA dead. So
That's just the way it goes and those powerful circles. That's how it works
Yeah, the fairs don't play man once they got you they got you especially even with you did I thought I thought he should have got more time
But you know the American
Well, the people that are around him, those people that are around him, you know what I mean,
they even have the feds in their pocket, because even the guy that is on Trump's administration,
and Amanda, if she's still up here, she might be able to help me a little bit,
but there's a dude that's on Trump's administration now that actually was Epstein's
prosecutor back in the day, and that's who gave him the sweetheart drill.
You know what I'm talking about, Amanda?
You had not said this to me.
I would have, it was on the tip of my tongue.
I cannot think of it.
Acosta?
Yes, that's it, Acosta.
Yep, and so, and actually.
Isn't that like somebody we know?
David, David Acosta?
What did you say?
Yeah, what did you say?
No, Billy.
That's somebody we know's last name.
Oh, yes, yes.
I know what you're referring to.
Who?
Yeah, we can't say it's dark thing, but.
You know you are see
Hey, Marcy. So but yeah, it was just
So when you have people like that around you, you know what I mean?
Like he gets away with it and not only that but he's also he did he was taught into Trump and Epstein as well
If you go back into your research back in the day, they were he was right there on my circle
So I'm just saying like hey, it's that noise
I don't know it's not me
Somebody got a rat in a house, man
In the desert out there with some camels
See if mice out there desert desert
This is not no damn field mice and there's not no damn camel spiders. Okay, you know Paul's been to Gaza
Apollo as Apollo sounds. It sounds to me. He's been around the world and back
I've been around the world and now y'all y'all
How many times you know you left your your hood
How many times I left my hood so something here you go
This was gonna say the Apollo Apollo bro, this is what I want to convey to you every time we have that we have dialogue
I always tell you that you over generalize shit cuz you always you put a
Stigmatic
I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from there, I'm from
There's a guy that did this to ask them and like people like come on man. Oh and speaking of ice
They're using chemical agents by the way guys. I read that over. Yeah
Yes, there. No, it's not okay because I know exactly what that shit does
That's what people have to understand they're not just you they're using on American stew that are not gang gangs in shit
that are fucking people up, that are hardworking people,
so they need to get their shit together
with their fucking rights.
White phosphorus, it's fucking disgusting.
I've seen it fucking peel people's skin off.
It's gross.
Somebody use that, can we?
Let me ask Apollo, of course, on Apollo, man.
You gotta quit thinking like that, man.
You gotta quit thinking that all brown
and black American automatically come from, you know,
an impoverished area out of the hood, bro.
It's not like that, bro.
You use automatically put that you so stigmatic what you're what you're out of
You're about freedom of speech. I really believe trees does live in the country because I can just hear the twang
I mean, I really do I'm telling you right now. I know where he's at and he's in the country
He's a more country than I am. Yeah, sure, but I'm from Lou. I was born in Mississippi. We migrated
I say that's a story on time. I was born in Mississippi. He migrated to the Midwest Louisville, Kentucky. I lived there
Until what I've been over great illegal or illegal or are you an illegal?
man shut your bitch ass up let me tell my story
i've been here where i've been now for six years but i i'm a country
okay i'm always gonna call eyes on you we're gonna call eyes on you
i grew up in the country too ain't nothing wrong with that
yeah that's what i'm looking at now yeah um speaking of the country i think it was wasn't
it at delta state where that young man was hanging from the tree
I don't I ain't hear about that. I don't know. I don't know. It was recently, right? Yeah
I know that yeah, I can't remember what city it was but I was a gym. Nick. I think it was Mississippi
Yes, and it's yeah
Blackfish yeah, well, you know Colin and she's big cancer, too
Colin Kaepernick paid for a separate
Autopsy and then now the truth has come out. I'll try to find the article and send it to you
Summer okay. Oh, yeah, it's
It's exactly what you think it is
Yeah, it's a lynching. Yes
Yeah, Jim nicking a beat a lynch me
Yeah, it's not even funny
well
I'm not trying to
Um you means here no who's here? Oh, it is your microphone. It's very quiet
Like lovely lady first of all, um, I don't know what you're talking about me at your zone is one around around plenty of times
So, uh, uh, yeah, why don't you slow down?
Well, she said lovely ladies, so it wouldn't be you know what God you can kiss my ass
It's the harvest man, it's beautiful. She's not as sweet as rain
I'm not as we is right now
You're in the toilet
Painting woman okay, can you stop hating woman? What's wrong with you, buddy? You fucking asshole. This is my best friend. You fucking loser
Then we call them a loser damn. Hey, what's up? How you doing it? How you doing?
I'm good. How are you?
So which are you looking at me? I never see you before
Thank you
So let me finish this real quick and then I'll shut up about the Mississippi thing his sister was apparently
Into it with a group of individuals and so the brother went to kind of help her and that's when the four
Other young men jumped into it
Maybe the sister did it. No the sister didn't
set up it was
You ever heard of the Duke Lacrosse
Case yeah, it was all bullshit. It was lies
But this involves I think some athletes like four white athletes. I'm not saying it's bullshit, but
Anyway
No, I've seen a picture of it he it really happened
Unfortunately, yeah, but just because you saw a picture of it doesn't mean it happened the way you think it happened
Well, they're investigating it. I mean now they originally thought it was a suicide and it's not they need to investigate it
They brought their asses in
What happened to him
Why is it Kathy?
That sounds familiar, yes.
He was talking about the EPSCEI and stuff, and then he, like, said, if I die, I do not, you know, commit SUICIDE.
Yes.
He jumped off a bridge like a week later.
He didn't jump off a bridge, and Vincent Foster didn't, none alive himself either.
Oh, Vincent Foster, oh, now you're going to make the clinsons, yeah.
Carolina her house burned down
Yeah, she did it
No, she didn't do it
She ruled against Trump and then the house and she had gotten desperate after that
That's why yeah, that's why when did that happen a couple days ago. No to this morning. It was burning
I take that back. I read it this morning. She could be only wasn't home either
she left to walk the dogs and
Well, I mean that cartoon talked about Epstein files and then he was aren't three days later. Yes, exactly
but
Think her husband got pretty injured in it. He had to jump from the top
You know down, you know, because in South Carolina everybody has their houses up high because of the water in case it floods
Their houses are on stilts and they broke their legs. Yeah, Aaron. How do you feel about Epstein?
Are you pro Epstein are you pro Epstein or like against him?
Like is so low
Yeah, we can't hear you at all psyche. Can you hear me now? It's a little better barely. There you go. Yeah
A little bit better in the private chat
Yeah, he's fine
I
the
Michael you need to leave and come back, honey. I don't know why I'm echoing all of a sudden
It's like why is the mic so big man?
We still can't hear you
Eat you Gotti
He's going to eat you?
Everyone wants to ask you a question.
Should I play the Gaudi song?
Why not?
We're going to play the Gaudi song.
Gaudi has a song?
Oh my gosh, everyone wants to hear it.
I want a song.
Well, you can have a song, Amanda.
Like, uh.
I'm not going to consider anything in the conversation.
I'll play my new song, and then maybe I'll play it.
Can you mute Michael before I have a stroke?
Yeah.
Michael, you have been muted off the island, I'm sorry.
Michael, give her the signal.
OK, he's muted.
So I made this video today.
Tell me how you like it.
Oh, you have to put it on.
Buddy, is that you?
No, no, no.
Oh my god.
This is a little Jordana.
Mr.
Okay, dude. Yeah
Michael needs to stop. I don't know what he's doing. I know Michael, you know what? You got to get a better microphone
You're gonna get into KZ territory. We're gonna kick you off and not leave back on
Okay, well, you know the song
Basically, I write the songs and then put them through the the AI right right. Yeah, I know if you catch that
They do songs like that with it with hip-hop
Yeah, basically your neighbors is just yeah, I'm saying it out. I should froze
Frozen shit frozen shit's a bad thing, buddy. Yeah, it's not cool
I just gave my person. Okay. Um, yeah, well, yeah, because if you well, this is actually really cool
Continue to play because everyone misses it but here it is
And you want to see my load? No, I'm sorry. You don't want to see who his load
Absolutely
I'll show you later. Okay
What's this one? Oh the panel verse
Sounds like Alex singing
on the chair, Rudy got flair, mumbles in the mix, we don't play fair, chat blowing up like
divine confessions, true bombs drop no time for confessions, you on logic, we bend it, drama,
we mend it, panel full of chaos, but the vibes transcending, if a troll wanna bark, we clap
back politely, with Andromalleus, watchin' nightly, welcome to psycho wakens tv, it's crazy, it's loud,
Find a psych, they cat, daddy, king of the stream
Welcome to Psych Awakens TV
With truth and madness, if the same plea
It's a family affair, it's this function supreme
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Yeah, pan-a-verse roll call
Bring your weirdest takes with mixed logic
With prophecy and cosmic stakes
Alyssa in the chat, she a mystery queen
DJ Electric got the beat, so
Panther strength divine she teams chaos with the stare and the line we don't do fake this trap's too real
We roast you kindly, but the love the deal got miles with swords keeping gates tight
They swing truth like justice in the moon like if this ups. Yeah, the coke keeps growing community wild
But the energy is flowing welcome to psych awaken CV is crazy as loud as bizarre believe me
the cat daddy king of the stream welcome to psycho wakens tv with truth and madness if the same t
it's a family
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Cards flip, candles drip, shadows in the mist
Trolls talk slick, but they cease to exist
We're half chaos, half or a cool flame
And every night's a ritual in Psyche's name
No scripts, no filters, no chillin' psych
We stream raw truth till the morning light
So grab your tea, grab your mic and vibe
We the strangest fam that's still alive
So pull up a chair, the rituals be gone
It's like a weekend's TV with a crazy one
This ain't YouTube
This is an underworld's talk show
You are now initiated
Father Psyche ain't spoken
Spoken
four and the ace and it's both the diamond and the heart.
I like the cat daddy part.
Thank you, thank you.
Also, I think Alexandra Mayer said she wants to do a song
about expounding on the cat daddy theme.
Okay, so let me just take this down.
I'm so sorry, there we go.
Okay, we're back.
I said this was really good too.
Thank you.
Two seconds.
What did you say?
I'm sorry, what did you say?
I said Shan does those really good too.
Okay.
She's the one that puts the AI on my songs.
Oh, so you do it.
So Erin, so you have a channel, Erin?
I do, but it's all on hers.
OK.
Because I'm a chicken.
OK, so your friend.
Chicken.
Yeah, well, there's already a chicken Andy,
and already a bronze chicken.
Oh my gosh, I do have to play the Alexander's Bita song.
I mean, did you guys see that whole one?
It's called BBC.
Love the echo.
Yeah, what happened to you?
Everybody's like everyone. Yeah, your legs are open again.
And I'm like, hey, buddy, buddy stop it.
Echo. Yes, I go in bed.
Stikey nothing got he says can hurt me. It's like, oh, yeah. Yeah
I'm gonna try this. Okay. Oh, yeah, it's pretty good. But like kick this out. I like Alexander Alexander actually has a
new song and I hope you guys like Alexander's new song
You know Alexander mayor
Hello. Thank you, Jamie. What is this? I can't hear anything. Is it on? It's like we
It's not playing on my TV either.
I'm sorry.
Let me retry it.
Uh-oh.
We lost somebody.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here we go.
I think it's like this.
I go like this.
This should work.
Okay.
Let me try this one.
One more time.
It doesn't say sharing, so I don't know why it's not working.
Okay.
Share.
Okay. Yeah, this is how it goes.
Do you see a black, do you see a black
screen now? No. No. I don't see a
wolf. Oh, and you take down the
wolf. That's why. Okay, hold on.
I got it. I got it. Did it come
down? No, it's black. Yep. Yeah.
Okay. Okay. Now, it's black.
Good. On the right track.
You know, it's really a lot of stuff we don't clean.
When I see everybody knows
Everything wrong, and I don't care
I'm on fire, put it out, and he's around
He can't be on the show, I'm in love
Happy to see all she wants
All right, I can just barely get it still. I mean, I put it the wrong I've heard the one
Let's see. I'm like
Okay, why is it going? Oh, here. I want my money back. No, no, it goes. I got it. I promise this. I promise this time
Okay, now do you see it? Okay. Yeah, it's black. Okay
I don't know what's working. Wow. Well, technical difficulties always copyright. Why am I, who's backstage? Apollo is backstage.
Apollo.
Are you there?
Yep, I'm here.
Oh, I know why it's because I changed these fucking settings. Okay. Let me see. I have to go look at this now
Okay, um shift videos for calm. Oh, okay. There it goes and automatically add. Okay, perfect
Okay, I mean I changed some settings and I should not have done that. Okay. I think we're still echoing two cells one more time one more time
Share screen
And he's a funny guy, you know truth song. I don't know. Yeah funny motherfucker
Okay, funny motherfucker
You roasted Apollo for like two hours up here. Yes
Okay, well now get ready for a chicken chicken roast because
I'm sorry. We're getting ready for chicken. I love chicken. I'm kind of hungry. Yeah
Hey everybody, you know, Bita really loves that BBC.
Wow.
Oh my.
I love it.
She's chasing Bronzeberg wherever he goes.
Heart on fire, she can't burn it out when he's around.
She can't help but shout out Bita loves that BBC.
It's all she wants.
It's all she needs.
Bronzeberg's the one.
Going late at night, he's caught in his feet
Every word he drops is all she needs
Dreaming about the day, he'll drive out her way
In her wild wild heart, he's a burning flame
He loves that BBC, it's all she wants
It's all she needs, transverts go on
She can't deny, she's the reason for that sparkle in her eyes
For all this Bronzeberg bride, she thinks about him every night.
She got the cock!
He loved it.
It's all she wants.
It's all she meets.
Bronzeberg's the one she can't deny.
Her heart takes flight whenever he goes live.
Okay
Because she did she put herself in it
Authentic it's more flattering than
She did a whole song and dance number for God's sake
You gotta appreciate that yes, I appreciate
Wow, strawberry shortcake is very upset.
Yeah, very.
You didn't like that strawberry shortcake? Oh, no.
I love that in the end she got the cock, you know?
In the end she catch it.
Well, woman, you should get it.
If you chase after that much, eventually you should get it.
Well, guys, don't call her cock hungry or whatever.
I love that bird. Very pretty.
well yeah he's also there's a bronze bird in my uh the haters club and uh it's a bronze one
go for the gold you need to go for the gold not the bronze um well there's my haters club video
like um you know because he has like you know whole lives about me um
a bronze bird?
Bronze bird.
Well, his name is Bronze Bird.
Oh.
Okay.
Sorry.
No.
I forgot I can drop links.
Actually, you know, I would hope that she has such a humor about it because that's
not even like a mean song.
That is just kind of, kind of cute.
It was kind of cute.
I mean, all it is is like, you know.
Spin the crash out, huh?
Well, no ghosts.
Oh, here's ghosts.
Come on, ghosts.
Ghosts actually are top donor energy, right?
Um, it goes, actually donated for Ghosttoberfest all week, all, no, all month long it's Ghosttoberfest.
Puts like you, Wicked Shadow.
Um, I don't want BBC, it's too big for me.
I just want a British Broadcasting System.
Actually, I don't even want a black-eyed stinger near me because it's like, they're actually big for me too.
Okay.
So it's very easy.
Ah, it's classic that he said that.
Get away from me.
Is uh, what's his name again?
Who? Me?
No
Bronzeberg
No, you said something about ghosts. Oh ghosts arbiter. He's arbiter in the chat. Yeah, Arbiter. Oh, okay
Except for you stream the other night. Oh, yeah, well, yeah ghost uh ghost donated like
Large a large amount of
Ghost you can donate to me that would be just fine
Well, wait, and you do have a panel. Yeah, did you stream yard? I don't know what you need
He loves he loves he loves arguing with people or goes to an argue with this woman. I got you
Okay. Yes, I need money
He loves a good debate
Ma'am and sir, oh
Hold on why are you on Rowdy Rowdy? Hold on. Who is that? Oh, it's Rick Flair. Okay, Rick Flair. Truth Son is back
Did you post your channel yet? Truth Son or are you a mod?
I'm guessing you're not a mod
Be the bashing bishes. Okay. Well, do you want to see what beat it said about me?
Talk about that and it's like and I was like apologetic and everything and then she like
Get out of here, and then she made me feel bad because she started crying and
Like, you know, I don't like to hear anybody crying and it's like so upset about me. What about my feelings?
How about I was hurt too? No, it's all like my fault, right?
I don't know, maybe it is.
Hello, it's Crystal Ghost.
She went to acting school.
It's not.
Yeah, she probably did.
Hello, Crystal Ghost, how are you?
Uh-oh.
He crashed out.
Yeah, it was caused by Psyche.
OK, let me just go.
Ghost.
Yes, sir.
Are you going to debate Aaron?
About what?
Whatever.
Oh, well, I mean, I guess it would depend on, I mean,
I guess whatever you want to debate about.
I want to debate you, but after you've done...
I'll go fucking five times in the morning, I wasn't really looking for one, but I'm down.
After you're done debating here, I'll debate you about something else.
Go ahead and debate him, because I have no idea what to debate over.
Well, you don't have a debate in you? Okay.
No.
We'll go so I want to debate
What do you want? I wanted to debate you about
Hitler being right about World War two. I don't know if that's necessary. We can talk about that on a sex panel
We can discuss it, but I don't know if we can do it here
Okay, well he left and
Or fell down and now we have a follow so you could debate with a follow
I'd like to have a topic if you guys don't mind. Sure
The fuck is everybody so equity tonight the fuck's going on
Hey, I'll debate you a crucible man, I'll debate your car
To me dude, I'm a friendly guy
So far friendly ghost
family goes
It goes you like a pale frog. He is a pale frog
You're like you're like what you like do like a little kid from king of the hill like you're like Bobby
Seen as the smartest retard I know sir you say what you heard me
Now, let me speak more clearly in this little piece of bubblegum. You like the bottom of my shoe backboard
Fat Power Ranger shut your nose talking to me
You're the one that talked to me don't fuck
My own talking to you in that sentiment. I'm talking to Apollo
Now I can talk to you such a refrigerator body ass up big body. You got a BMW body body made wrong
You ship like an ironing board fat enough that your ass up
What's I can what's I'm a psychic and everybody go man
I don't know.
I just hate Donnie. That was it.
I don't understand why.
Yeah, they don't hate me.
No, he's my best friend.
Oh, they do.
They love me.
You actually understand what the fuck he's saying?
Sometimes.
Yeah, I mean half-assed.
This is a picture of Apollo, by the way.
Oh, he's adorable. I love your hat.
Yeah, that's why he he talks the way he does because of that. He's like that old perverted old perverted guy from motherfucking
Uh, what's the name of that guy? So family guy? Yeah
What is his name? Um, old perverted guy
Oh, is it Herbert. Yeah, you're right
Herbert the pervert or so. I hate family guy. I really do
I
Should cringe as hell man. Yeah mad cringy. Yeah, fuck that. Yes
Hey, what's up page long time no see the link
The page cool message of people mad by the way, so you got even help from the link
Did I like I
Mean it was your fucking name I
Forget that I can post links
I'm new to this shit cops are coming to get me
God you're gonna have to bail me out of jail. I'll bail you out. Okay. Thank you
Nothing more than 500 though
So I can't do anything major
Your lawyer if you need one
Get banned money and a lawyer. He's just gonna debate. He's not gonna try to get you out
kind of what you do in court
As long as he debates the judge and to let me go
You scared to debate ghost
You said I'm scared to do what
You're scared to debate go you scared to debate ice. How's that about that?
and when you say eyes you're scared to debate a heist asian right now go to call them right now
debate in one on one right now i bet you won't ghost one true some loss again
Imagine this motherfucker asking a phone while you're trying to order some shit some shit fried rice
He answered the phone, but didn't you rich chicken fried rice?
Now like no man, you a Chinese person to phone man, and I know you smile
You work that really good
Very you don't you don't think he's funny. Oh, I think he's very funny
I
Don't fuck me now. He wasn't he merely a minute or not a time. I go live. He's either in the bushes. I eat your comment in the chat
Say that he's had a couple good ones tonight, I'm not gonna lie
He Apollo's in Apollo's intrigued by the American coach of the black
I ain't gonna say the black yeah, but he
He's intrigued by us black Americans because he just left a comment on my chat
He's left a comment on one of my videos. I forgot what you said you told you asked me to teach you how to say something
I forgot what you said
So he's intrigued
What did comment did you leave a
American culture you are a very good to represent us
You're intrigued by it, bro. You know you are. You want to learn
Yeah, but stupidity
When you're with your family try to talk like this you telling your you be telling your wife shit your bitch
We had to cancel your order motherfucker keep going through some keep going make a fool out of yourself
You said what Mary time you talk you make a fool of yourself man
And ghost is completely quiet. What is happening right now? It's 4 30
No, it's a scream
No, it's not would you like would you like a crash out? Oh
Please I see those so rarely for $400. I'll give you a crash out
Didn't I just say I was poor that's the going right now 400
399 but you know same thing
Well, there's no tax on it
It's a it's a bargain
I might give it to you for free. I don't understand a fucking thing. He's saying
I'm not talking about cuz he's kind of might be a little bit of a dumb dumb. I'll see and I don't his accent is fucking me all of
I'll be the translator go ahead
Translate this
Can you say hi, my name is Apollo
Yeah, put this man on hook don't find this man, which I try to do this man Aaron the folly store
I'm trying to get the man. I'm trying to get him to speak English. I'll be completely honest with you
That is my purpose here. I'm trying to get what I give him credit for how many how many different languages you know speak
He's but not alert it might not be, you know
Dr. Parl, but he at least he tries man cuz I don't ran into some foreign as to where I'm like man
What do what the hell you talking about? But at least it can't a lot of people can't speak different languages man
So Paula Paula, what's that folly store?
How are you so if I list oh, yeah
Thank you
You are like
You learn Spanish so you join a fucking Spanish speaking podcast like the least he's trying even though they don't the fuck you're talking about it's like I
Mean, I guess you are trying
If an alien came right now you and they start they start talking that tuning in language
You won't understand that the fuck they was talking about the same thing with this alien right here. We don't know
I'm pretty sure they would understand math though. I'm pretty sure how that theory goes
You know pie if the universal language, I mean, I love pie
Like that like sixth grade. I think I think there's no the only pop the only pilot ghost that ass knows the oatmeal cream pie in his pocket
The only person in this pie here, the only pie you know is the old meal crea-
You better be nice.
This is the zebra cake in your pocket, motherfucker.
You leaving a poem hate, uh, you know bore you sir, but if you contribute
If I restore if you do leave
Apollo be right back man, he be talking this shit. He'll be right. He'll be right back up on the panel
He'll be in the trees watching with knockers and all man
Can you debate another foreign language
Um, no, I used to be dumb dumb pretty fucking good though. I'm not gonna lie
He really did did man, which I'll be easy don't like to get up out of here man
He's gonna shut up man. You have to ease the shot to Gatti man. Shout out the site. Thanks a lot man. I appreciate it man
Nice to meet you soon. Hi for sure
Better that down
This is a better run. He had me dying earlier. Oh fuck. I like the whole fucking half hour fucking on the floor
Wait, who was true song? Oh, he was ripping fucking Apollo to shreds
$400 to bought Robbie why not
We do it for free
No.
I like that.
Psyche, you need to come back up here.
I want you to pull a card for me, please.
Yeah, how many thousands have you given Psyche Ghost?
Um, enough to block you, motherfucker.
Go ahead, blow another four grand.
You know, sir, you know for God, you know, you're kind of special
You'd fucking
Great gift if I did give that, you know another for grand or what did we just said just to block you?
I think that'd be a fair gift to you sir for what a year
No, indefinitely
Right
It's not a whole new channel just have me up again
By the way
No, actually, I'm not gonna bring it up because that's a I don't bring up the other YouTube channels
Which one okay the TPP. Oh, yeah, when I fucked your boy up
Which one who Renee I
Don't know did I did I kick his ass to you probably I don't know
What are you talking about?
This one has Bruno on there, right? Yeah, Bruno's over there. Yeah, yeah
Did you not see that guy I'm sure you were there I don't I don't think I saw that one
Now look it up
Is that why you're bent?
Yeah
How much how much money did people pay or what did they ban me for free free?
What was the percentage looking like
To not ban you no too bad. Well either way what did it look like? It was unanimous to ban you
unanimous, I mean they had to have a poll if they're gonna make a fucking yeah, and it was a hundred to zero
Nobody wanted to
So, okay, Paige.
Oh, I forgot to ask Paige, did you get my comment?
Or did I forget to comment?
Well, Paige Sykes not here, so if you're late for there,
you can join and give Erin a card reading.
Well, Sykes has to let her up, that's what she's saying.
Oh, shit, my bad, all right.
Yeah, I guess I didn't read them.
Like sleeping now you can form bomb the channel hold on
I thought there was gonna be a debate. What do you guys want?
Against who who's debating? I give you whatever you want in God
You know what
We won't let me debate. I tried to debate. I mean, I wasn't allowed to debate
And when did that happen
Earlier he kicked me off the panel. Oh, well, maybe I don't know. I wasn't here. I don't know what happened
No, you were here. Oh
Page has a new kitty
Why do you have a picture of my uncle as your profile your uncle
Well, your uncle has big titties. Uncle Jaycee. Is that what that is? Uncle Jaycee.
This is a bit of a Frankenstein. It's a very short kick. I don't think that's how he would spell them.
I think it's just DUM. DUM space DUM. It's not that hard people. Very common.
Very common, it's beautiful, it's lovely, it might even be the greatest thing I've ever been said.
Aaron, if I look like this, would you still like me if I look like this?
Absolutely, can I put it on your head, Dan?
Yeah, you can.
Okay, thank you.
Danielson!
No, not Danielson.
You look like the character from The Karate Kid from the movie about Old Movie.
Not The Karate Kid.
Back when you're about 30 years old, I forgot this guy's name. What was his name?
Yoshi
The name's Yoshi. I think it was something Takahashi. That's Takahashi
Takashi Takashi, that's it
That's a big hero by the way
From what big hero six you fucking nerd
It's also like in big hero six. Oh my god
Strawberry shortcake, I was just teasing you. I know how dumb this felt
Okay, Michael, what do you mean with the 52 page? I'm sorry to say this but uh, I
Zoomed in on you. I zoomed in on your picture page, right? Looks like you got a booger hanging from your nose
I'm not joking. I'm not fucking joking. Do you want me to show you? Hold on, hold on.
Oh, I'm scared.
By the way, can you spell Dumb Dumb for me?
The way you spell it, or she does?
No, I asked you the question.
Hold on, let me show you this.
Well, you got to tell me which one, because they're spelled two different ways.
I'm always saying this because we're friends.
Intelligence spooks, okay.
I'm just gonna nod my head and pretend I know what you're talking about Michael here it comes
She's gonna investigate right now
If you're investigating, I'm showing you on the big screen. Well, you can't be on the big big screen
Here it comes see. Oh
That is a booger. That's
That's something akin of a book
That is so mean beautiful smile, but
Just wipe that beautiful smile, but a big fucking burger
Prairie booger
Okay, I'm just kidding and don't pull a card from me either paid. I was just kidding
Just looking out for your kids
Okay, Michael's kind of scaring me
Michael knows all about the NSA. Don't worry about him the NSA the NSA the CIA the FBI all that stuff
I gotta get that dude up just up here not Apollo the other guy
He said why don't you debate an ice agent?
God that was good funny truth fucking funny
You had me speechless man, I was fucking dying laughing for real. Oh, yeah, yeah, he's he's great. He's really fucking good
That's my type of humor right there
What they tell him that he can debate an ice agent
They said you're scared to be a ghost and he's like you should be scared to debate an ice agent
Oh God
A lot of people, you know, they think they could talk a lot of shit, but they get very sensitive up here
You know Aaron, you know, I kind of feel like and I don't want to debate about it
But I kind of feel like you're the reason why Apollo left. I did say you didn't speak English, but I think you kind of upset him
He left because of me
Well, he said that you bored him. Oh, that's very true. I tend to have that impression
I mean, I would I would have to make yards and I kind of got he's kind of a born one. I think I am very boring. Yeah, it's true
Why do you think?
There's a reason I don't fucking stream
I
Just dream but I only have like
I need people to play off of
This is true. You know
So play off of them ghosts. Oh, you know what it is
You're gonna be a fuck this is to be on a stream for like 10 hours and just talk about yourself
So both of these stream owners are fucking all about
Themselves, I'm sorry Jamie. What'd I say that wasn't true?
Like hours and hours on end
Everything everything I say is not true. Hey Mel's in the chat. Hi
I see her forever
Melanie hello
Raptors Lamborghini and the skies welcome back Wow
Why she she waits until the lick the last minute right before I'm leaving
and she says, oh, you always
leave when I come up.
Oh, she can't.
Oh, we got a debate going to
happen, huh?
She can't come up.
Oh, yeah, never mind.
Hey, Michael, can you speak in a
coherent sentence, maybe?
Oh, okay.
I don't know what debating I've never heard you have a real debate one time. Yeah, I mean either I don't even actually know how to debate
One big scam, you know if you some were competent enough and you just call people dumb dumb as you kind of get away with it
Let's see what it looks like done spoke to you and oh, yeah
Much better. Oh, yeah, we can't see anything. Oh
What's that what's that in the we can see the glare on your glasses are you watching porn?
She's watching porn look at you can see it in the glasses
If the paranormal techniques are so easy Michael we have an example demonstration
I mean, she has asked for a little bit of a burden of proof.
You made the claim, sir.
She's being smart right now.
She's asked for a little burden of proof.
You hear it?
The burden of proof.
Yeah, if you make a claim, Don, if you make a claim,
I'm sure you know this already.
The burden of proof is on the person.
Walks a beat in the city life
Flashin' blues under New York nights
But his heart's up north where the river's run free
With a blonde hair, beauty from April Country
He's got a badge of dream and a thing for a laugh
Caught a glimpse of her smile
Now he's doin' the math
From the Bronx to the Bush
Oh, he's thinkin' real deep
Paige, are you the one I've been missin' in my sleep?
Paige!
She's gutting the trout. He's eating steak somewhere in the middle. They both take a break
He'd trade his night stick for a fishing pole chase her laughter like it's his patrol page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day and this cop's got one hell of a line to say